(This program may contain indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Fall is much closer this morning, with the wind growing cooler.)
Hello.
- What is this? - There are a lot of...
pretty places these days.
(They are in Cheorwon in Gangwon Province today.)
We've been here before, right?
- Hello. - I remember being here.
- Hello. - We got a penalty here.
(I remember.)
- We went up riding something. - This is...
I remember everything.
We came here before.
(They came to the Cheorwon History and Culture Park in 2022.)
I totally remember it.
Hello. When did we come here?
We broke eggs here.
(Seok Sam lost yet another memory.)
- Right. - We broke eggs over there.
- This is the place. - On the street.
(He doesn't remember.)
That's right. It was Cheorwon.
Star Ha is here.
- Hey. - Star Ha.
(Haha had his Seoul fan concert the day before the shoot.)
All right.
- Star Ha. - Our Star Ha.
All of our staff members went to his concert.
("We Never Die")
- Right. They all came. - Star Ha.
(Truly touched)
(And a man quietly follows behind.)
Our Star Ha.
All of our staff members went to his concert.
(His 12th appearance, Heo Kyung Hwan)
We have both Star Ha and Star Heo.
Kyung Hwan just shows up quietly.
- Come over here. - It's not like...
(Since it is his 12th visit, he just comes in on his own.)
- Go over there. - there's anyone...
- You're a guest. - specifically looking out for me.
One of the writers is supposed to come and take care of me...
Stay quiet. It's time for the opening.
"Stay quiet?"
We have a lot to talk about.
(They have a lot to say after 2 weeks off the air.)
- We have a lot to talk about. - Let us talk first.
- The thing is... - We have a mountain of things.
Kyung Hwan came all the way here to Cheorwon as a guest today.
- And this is a two-day trip. - Right.
(They are having an overnight shoot today.)
We needed someone who was available...
(Guest requirements: Available schedule,)
- and had great chemistry with us. - Sure.
(chemistry with the members)
- Kyung Hwan was the only option. - Right.
(The exclusive guest in Cheorwon, Heo Kyung Hwan)
I've been really busy, so I'm available for only two days.
- Kyung Hwan is... - I have only two days.
He's really busy.
Actually, he came here without his manager.
- Seriously? - You came without your manager?
My manager was so tired that he didn't pick up his phone today.
- Seriously? - So...
(His manager didn't show up for the early-morning departure.)
I rushed over by myself.
- That's why... - So I'm really tired now.
(Touchy)
- Your eyes are so puffy. - That's right.
(No wonder.)
- So he's wearing sunglasses. - He's not wearing makeup.
- Right. - His manager...
(He hurriedly came to Cheorwon without putting on makeup.)
must be really flustered now.
- That's true. - Of course.
- So... - What happened? Did he sleep in?
He meant to charge his phone, but it must not have charged.
He called me on my way here, so I texted him, "You're out."
(You're out.)
Everything happens for a reason, you know.
- "You're out." - Everything happens for a reason.
- Everybody makes mistakes. - It happens to everyone.
Even my manager does that sometimes.
(Easily letting him off the hook)
- It happens to everyone. - Right. It happens.
You've got to cut them some slack once or twice a year.
- They're only human, after all. - Right.
(It happened to be the day of the Cheorwon shoot.)
- Of course. - You sleep in sometimes.
But things always go well on days like this.
(Optimistic)
- When things are hectic... - It goes well on days like this?
I don't think you're being funny today.
Right. Wait.
(Mr. Muscles ruins the mood from the start.)
- Hang on. We haven't done anything. - He's not so funny.
- Why would you say that? - He's less funny than usual today.
(Help me.)
- Don't be like that. - Mr. Marine, what's wrong with you?
- "Mr. Marine?" - Jong Kook...
- went to Haha's concert, - He's cute.
(I know why.)
and Kyung Hwan suddenly said this to Jong Kook.
When Jong Kook was filming "Gym Jong Kook" there,
Kyung Hwan said, "Why are you filming it without permission?"
Then Jong Kook told him, "Okay. So that's what you do."
- "Okay. I get it." - Star Heo.
(Star Heo delivers a sharp rebuke with authority.)
- What a star. - He's become a star, and now...
And while Haha was performing, we all did this, you know.
When we were all doing this, Kyung Hwan was like this alone.
(Flicking his fingers)
I see. He acts like a big shot.
(Star Heo cheered efficiently without breaking a sweat.)
He's a real star now.
So Jong Kook was like, "Okay. I get it now."
- Seriously... - My goodness.
- So, Haha... - We should talk about his concert.
- Haha had a fan concert yesterday. - Yesterday.
(Haha's solo concert in Seoul "We Never Die" sells out.)
How was it? I heard it was super fun.
- It was a lot of fun. - They all came.
(An encore show was opened due to popular demand.)
It was really...
(Haha never dies.)
Haha!
I was shouting this so much yesterday...
- that my voice is completely shot. - Se Chan hyped the crowd up a lot.
- Right. I was so grateful. - Se Chan sang along to the songs.
- Right. - You didn't come on free invites.
(Thank you.)
- You actually paid for the tickets. - Right. I paid 99 dollars.
It was a huge help.
Haha didn't come to my concert, but I went to his.
(Bitter)
Why are you saying that?
- What? - Oh, right.
- He left at 6:10pm. - You left at 6:10pm, right?
- To play soccer. - I just had to play soccer.
(Unapologetic)
(He left right on the dot after watching for 1 hour.)
- My goodness. - I mean...
But it started at 5pm.
Right in the middle of the concert, Jong Kook suddenly stood up...
and packed his stuff. So I asked, "Where are you going?"
(Soccer comes before Haha's first fan concert.)
- He stopped me. - "I have to go play soccer."
(Relentless love for soccer of the future KFA president)
How was the concert? I couldn't go because of work.
(Curious)
- How was it? - The most...
- Were you proud? - The freshest...
and best live performance was Jae Seok's.
- I performed... - Did you perform live?
- You sang? - It was a real live performance.
- I sang live after a long time. - What did you sing?
(He did a live performance on the spot when asked.)
I was asked to sing "Redevelopment of Love."
He sang live without even a backing track.
(Yu San Seul showed off a flawless performance...)
(despite the sudden request.)
It's live.
- My goodness. - Hey.
- It was pure live. - You did a great job.
It was a real live performance.
Though it was my concert, my social media is...
filled with clips of Jae Seok's performance.
People say my live performance was better than the concert's headliner.
Over half the audience went...
- just to see Jae Seok. - That's true.
It must've been great.
- That was so funny. - Please do it again next time.
(Joining today's race is national star Yu San Seul.)
- He asks you to do it again. - That was hilarious.
Today, for a trip to Cheorwon, a perfect place for traveling,
we prepared the Rip and Crush Cheorwon Race.
Rip and Crush Cheorwon!
Say it for us. Rip and Crush Cheorwon!
- Rip and Crush Cheorwon! - Rip and Crush Cheorwon!
All right.
I'll reveal the bingo board to be used in today's race.
(Proud)
(Today's race features a bingo board.)
- Okay. - We have a board?
There's Military Camp Training?
- What? Military Camp Training? - There's Military Camp Training?
That's because there are...
(Rip and Crush Cheorwon Bingo Board)
- many military bases in Cheorwon. - That's true.
The nine slots on the bingo board...
(The 9 bingo slots have Cheorwon travel spots written on them.)
(Mount Soi Observatory, Private room 1)
have Cheorwon travel spots written on them.
(Mount Soi Observatory)
We have to complete one line of bingo by 4pm to succeed.
(Columnar Joints)
- By 4pm? - Yes.
There will be missions at each spot.
(Maewoldae Falls)
You have to clear the mission to claim the slot.
(They will get the slot if they succeed in the mission.)
(Military Camp Training)
If we fail to complete the bingo within the time limit,
(Hantan River Rafting)
- all of you get a penalty. - All of us?
(Beekeeping Experience)
So we have to complete the bingo.
- This is... - What's written at the bottom?
Prizes are written underneath the travel spots.
(Each slot has a prize.)
They're the prizes.
The prizes are what you need for tonight's accommodation.
(When a line is finished, they get the prize on the line.)
- We get a private room if we win? - Yes.
(They even have a private room to rest in comfort.)
- That's what I need. - It's great.
- Is it a group room? - I like having a private room.
- That would be great. - I like having a private cabin.
Some of us, including me, snore loudly when we sleep.
- That's me. - Seok Jin grinds his teeth.
- He does. - Right.
(Grinding)
Seok Jin takes his revenge in his sleep.
(In his sleep.)
"I won't let you get away with it."
He must've lived such a life full of grievances.
You should let me take the private cabin, then.
(Bold-faced)
- What? - Let me sleep in the private cabin.
(Forget it!)
- No way. - We can't do that.
- That's the best one. - We have to see how it goes.
(He won't give it up.)
Prizes will be awarded for the claimed slots of the bingo.
Let's go to the Mount Soi Observatory in the middle first.
(The middle)
- Mount Soi Observatory. - All right.
- We have to claim this first. - We should.
(Mount Soi Observatory, Private room 1)
Of course.
Then, the first destination is...
- Mount Soi Observatory. - Mount Soi Observatory.
(Their first destination for Rip and Crush Cheorwon...)
We have to claim the one in the center.
(is Mount Soi Observatory.)
- Let's go. - Mount Soi Observatory.
- All right. - It's the Mount Soi Observatory.
(The current time is 10am. The mission begins.)
- Let's go. - Let's go!
We're driving non-stop, baby
(They head out to Mount Soi.)
That's my manager.
- He's finally here. - He's here.
- He's... - My manager is here.
He rushed over, kicking up a cloud of dust.
He must've been really flustered.
- When he woke up in the morning... - He must've been really surprised.
Looking back, we totally get how he felt.
(Thanks to that, his celebrity got lots of screen time in the opening.)
So you wouldn't find it upsetting.
- He always tries his best. - I know.
But it seems like you got your hair done.
- No. - Did you style your hair yourself?
(The cosmetology major does his own hair and makeup.)
Yes.
He majored in cosmetology.
I was so stressed out and kept running my hands through my hair,
so now it's all greasy.
(Bursting into laughter)
- It's greasy? - Yes.
That's a lie.
- That's true. - I kept doing this.
Just let it go.
That's the kind of joke I like.
(Haha loves Kyung Hwan's jokes.)
- This? - Yes.
By the way, the dyed hair really suits you.
(Thank you.)
Thanks.
He's Lee Kang In's brother.
If I dyed my hair like that, I'd probably go bald, right?
(Envious)
I was worried about it too,
- It's okay? - but it turned out fine.
- How about bleaching it white? - Seok Jin.
- That would be so weird. - I want to give it a try.
- Don't do it. - Who are you to say that?
- Are you a fashion leader or what? - I'm your senior.
- It's not like... - Junior comedians, gather later.
(Oh, really?)
- Heo Kyung Hwan. - It's your fault.
(KBS 7th term, KBS 10th term, KBS 22nd term)
- You should teach them a lesson. - I should.
Are you going to get beaten up today?
- You'll see. - At around 2am,
(Gather up.)
when the cameras are off, I'll teach him a lesson.
I've staked my destiny on this. My life is on the line.
- His destiny? - I'm not going.
- This is about my pride. - The comedian from SBS, too.
(Se Chan)
- I'll be there. - You should carry him out.
- What? - I do whatever my senior says.
(At your service.)
You'll be carrying the wooden logs, just so you know.
(Early-morning log training is due.)
Wooden logs?
- Can I shoot a short clip? - Yes, you can.
It will easily hit 100 million views.
- "This is crazy!" - The senior...
"Today is Seok Jin's turn to take a beating."
That's it.
(While Junior Jee continues to get a hard time...)
He's getting beaten up now.
Shaking his legs, he says, "I'm not going."
Thank you.
(They arrived at the first bingo spot.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Thank you. - Let's go.
What is this place?
(Lush greenery unfolds before their eyes.)
- Hang on. This is... - I've seen this before.
This is so cool.
It's beautiful. Even the sky is so pretty.
(Mount Soi is perfect for a fall hike!)
- It's really pretty. - I love this place.
(What kind of mission will they get in the heart of Cheorwon’s nature?)
- It's so pretty. - It smells nice.
The smell of the mountains.
Jee Seok Sam! This is the place you and I climbed up together.
- That's right. - This is it?
(Seok Sam and Jae Seok walked this trail...)
- We hiked up here. - Right.
While the other members rode something up,
(as a penalty 4 years ago.)
- you and I had to walk. - Exactly.
- This is it. - Right.
There was even a bunker here, like a military zone.
(Ji Hyo also remembers that there was a bunker here.)
I think we had some mission up there.
We've been here before.
Let me tell you the mission for the Mount Soi Observatory.
(The mission for them at Mount Soi...)
It's called This Is What Hiking Is All About.
(Satisfied)
Now you will hike all the way up to the Mount Soi Observatory.
(They will hike all the way up to the observatory.)
Today, it will be totally...
(They already hate it since they have experience.)
This mountain is pretty high.
- Really? - How long did it take last time?
It took quite a while.
How much further do we have to go?
(The hiking course sucked the energy out of them 4 years ago.)
This mountain is quite high.
(An endless uphill climb all the way to the peak)
- It's a long course. - Slope,
why are you refusing to compromise with the world?
(It will be even more grueling with the late-fall heat.)
- It's hot. - Yes, it's hot.
This is hard.
There are four themed courses set...
(Course 1, Course 2, Course 3, Course 4)
- up along the trail. - Okay.
In each course, only the members who resist the temptations...
(Tempting supplies await on each course.)
- will be rewarded with a coin. - What temptation?
You'll get one coin each time you resist a temptation.
(Course 1, Course 2, Course 3, Course 4)
- They'll accumulate as you go. - Okay.
(Rip and Crush Cheorwon Bingo Board)
When you reach the summit,
you'll need to hand in a total of 25 coins.
(Mount Soi Observatory, Private room 1)
- But this is... - How bad could the temptations be?
I know. We can just ignore them.
I guess there are things like water, delicious snacks,
(In the middle of the course)
or ramyeon along the way.
I won't be able to hold back. My stomach is empty now.
(The Tiger Moths are already making excuses in advance.)
- Me too. I didn't have breakfast. - I'm hungry.
Let's just eat.
- I'll just... - If it's coffee, I'll fall for it.
- I want coffee. - I have to drink coffee.
(Caffeine seekers are popping up here and there.)
- Is there an iced Americano? - Coffee.
If I had coffee, I could go straight up.
I prefer beans with some acidity.
(His personal preference)
You can check it out as you go up.
(Will they be able to resist temptation and make it to the top?)
- The mission starts now. - Okay.
This is way higher than it looks.
(They start hiking their way up to the observatory.)
- The slope is pretty steep too. - It's steep.
- Jong Kook seems to like it. - Yes.
- I love it. - This is perfect, isn't it?
(Kim Muscles loves the steep hiking trail.)
- For a leg workout. - I do incline walking...
- Okay. - on the treadmill every morning.
- So actual hiking is even better. - Right.
Let's have some coffee. I want to drink coffee.
(Already?)
I'm weak to the temptation of coffee.
Ye Eun, if there's coffee, are you going to drink it?
(Right away)
Yes.
- We have to save up those coins. - You have to hold back.
(Baffled)
- We need to save up the coins. - Don't be tempted.
Then let's share a cup of coffee.
That's not a bad idea.
(Not having it is not an option.)
- Let's split one together. - Even if you share a cup of coffee,
you still lose as many coins as the people who drank it.
(Even if they share, those who eat can't get coins.)
- Okay. - Then, we should all have our own.
- Let's just drink one each. - If that's the case,
- we should just drink separately. - I can resist...
pretty much any temptation.
I actually want to fall for a temptation.
(Desire-free Mr. Kim is full of confidence.)
That's how I feel.
There might be a temptation to take a monorail along the way.
(It has already been 5 minutes since they started the hike.)
- Here... - That could be the temptation.
It's starting to get hot.
It's hot.
(Current temperature: 31°C)
I hate sweating.
I should've worn short sleeves.
- I should've worn short sleeves. - I need short sleeves.
(The drastic temperature swing has the sweat starting to pour.)
- Cheorwon... - There are mosquitoes.
I heard Cheorwon was supposed to be cool.
- No one knows. - Come here.
(It's hot and exhausting,)
Hold my arm, Ji Hyo.
(with an endless uphill road.)
Why is this so hard?
- Ji Hyo is tired already. - I told you. It's steep.
(At that moment)
There's something over there. I see an icebox.
What's that?
(The first supply station welcomes the hikers.)
It's an icebox.
(Course 1: The first temptation)
- Why? - What is it?
I have to drink it.
(To cool off the heat in an instant,)
I have to drink what's there.
It's water.
(bone-chillingly cold water)
It's amazing.
(Haha stops in front of the tempting cold water.)
- Hey, it's not that bad. - What is it, Haha?
- What is it? - What?
(Coins gained in Course 1)
- Are you really that impatient? - Is it water?
This isn't right.
(They skip it without hesitation to secure their coins.)
- It's just water. - This isn't enough.
- Why would you want water? - He's right.
(They can't get the coin if they drink the water.)
How many coins do we get for this?
Only those who drink it fail to earn a coin.
We haven't even walked that far.
(Frustrated)
How can you drink water when we've barely walked?
- Touch this. - Just come here.
(It won't work.)
Can I take this then?
(Seok Sam chooses an R coin instead of water.)
- Shouldn't we get two each? - Hey, this is...
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook also earn one coin each.)
We have to go for the coffee.
Of course.
(Coins gained in Course 1)
Water isn't worth losing coins over.
Just come here.
(Ji Hyo and Ye Eun also hold back and choose R coins.)
Hurry and get over here.
- Hurry up. - This...
- I'll let it slide this once. - Just hold back once.
(They all resist temptation well, but...)
You have to be patient.
(Putting his hand in)
Hey, Yang Ssaebssaeb.
Hurry and get over here.
- What are you doing? - It's nice.
You can't put your hand back in after touching your face.
(Mr. Monkfish saves the water for his skin and keeps the coin.)
- What's wrong with that? - You can't put it back in.
You're not going to drink this anyway.
Come here.
(Warning)
Just dare to drink that water.
(Faced with a stern roar, they all pass on the water.)
It must be so cool.
There's no point in dressing...
(Meanwhile, the ones that headed out first...)
- according to the season anymore. - Jong Kook.
They say I look bulky...
when they see me from behind. What do you think?
- You do look bulked up. - Do I?
(Physical 60)
Right? Do I look bulky?
(Without emotion)
- Seriously, you look solid. - I do?
- All the hard work is paying off. - Are you proud?
(Proud)
Guys, lift heavy stuff.
(Feeling on top of the world thanks to the producer's flattery)
- Of course. - I haven't done it for long myself.
You have to work out.
This feels cool.
Of course. You should feel it.
Right.
(Running)
I have to take first place. I should be in the lead.
(Adrenaline overload)
I'm in first place.
- Where are you going? - Okay.
(Squeaking)
- Did your legs give out? - No.
- You just ran from here to there. - No.
(Sheepish)
You were like this just now.
(The playful senior found the perfect excuse to tease him.)
- No. That's not true. - Did you sprain your ankle?
- No. - Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
(For no reason)
This is nice.
That's a lie.
I remember this place.
This is really steep.
I don't usually go hiking.
(A dizzying slope with no end in sight)
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook are taking the lead.)
Yu Jae Seok is going too fast.
- Just hurry up. - I want to walk without sweating.
(Jae Seok strides forward...)
(into the lead without hesitation.)
It's too fast.
(The newbie weightlifter behind him is about to run out of energy.)
Here's the second course.
What's that?
(Course 2, protein bar)
The protein bar looks so good.
(Protein bars for a quick energy boost)
You do need that kind of stuff for hiking.
(Protein)
It has 25 grams of protein. That's pretty nice.
(He checks on the content.)
- The nutritional value is solid. - Gosh, this is...
(Seok Sam joins in late.)
This is what Jong Kook likes.
Right?
Seok Jin.
(Exhausted)
- Your face is totally sagging. - No.
- This is a protein bar. - When did you get here?
- You were just down there. - No.
- It's not here. - Was it someone else? Sorry.
(Sorry.)
- I'm sorry. - What's wrong with you?
(He's totally drained after going wild on his own.)
You look completely out of it.
I'll pass on it.
(Grabbing)
- But this is... - It will be really dry.
- I want to eat it. - It will make you thirsty.
You'd better save it and eat it later.
(Gulping)
Someone's over there.
(Just then, the slowpokes spot the leading group.)
They stopped over there.
Haha, let's just eat everything like crazy.
(Whispering)
- Will you eat it? - I'll just do as you say.
You're my variety show senior, so I should learn from you.
All right. This is Chapter One.
(Variety Shows Chapter 1: Eat what you are told not to eat.)
You have to eat what you're told not to eat.
You have to do what you're told not to do.
(Variety Shows Chapter 1: Do what you are told not to do.)
That's rule number one in variety shows.
- I should learn. - Let's just go there...
and eat right away. Let's go.
No. Wait, Se Chan.
(Stopping)
We should eat after everyone leaves.
(She is smart when it comes to food.)
You're right.
- Because... - Chapter Two.
Whatever you do, you have to do it behind people's backs.
Right.
Let's pretend we're saving up the coins.
We should do this behind their backs.
(The hyenas approach, mulling over the teachings.)
- We should send them ahead first. - Okay.
- There will be ramyeon. - Let's go.
(The older members leave after taking their coins.)
It looks delicious.
(Hesitating)
This looks just too good.
A protein bar?
(Seok Sam is on the verge of falling for the temptation.)
- I want to eat this. - No.
It's so hot.
If you eat it, you can't enjoy gukbap later.
(Stern)
- You can't eat it. - Okay.
- It will ruin your appetite. - I'm not craving this.
- Not this one. - Isn't it dangerous...
if Seok Jin goes low on sugar?
- No. - Will you be okay?
(They all pass Course 2 thanks to Haha,)
Hello.
(who has clear preferences.)
Good morning.
This is an intense leg workout.
(Ten minutes into the hike, they set off for Course 3.)
This isn't easy.
(Course 1, Course 2, Course 3, Course 4)
It's quite steep.
It's a very long hike.
(Panting)
Gosh, this is hard.
(Jae Seok is walking in the lead without a word.)
It's hot.
- I'm out of breath. - I'm tired.
(It's so hot.)
- Don't die. - This is so hard.
(Taking off)
You must be feeling hot in that denim jacket.
(They take off the fall outfits they tried so hard to put together.)
I want some coffee.
It's so hot.
(They're dazed by the early fall heat.)
- I'm sweating. - Me too.
If there's a cool sports drink, I'll drink it right away.
Give me some Americano.
(Desperate)
Give me some ice cream.
I'll eat ice cream right away.
- I want a cool Americano. - Haha,
(Only thinking of one thing)
imagine climbing halfway up there...
- and finding Pyongyang naengmyeon. - From a famous restaurant.
- How many coins? - Five coins.
- Then I'll eat it. - More importantly,
the noodles are served in a separate bowl.
(Detailed about food)
After I say I will eat it, they pour broth over the noodles.
(While they are lost in happy thoughts, tired from the heat...)
We all would want to eat it.
- Right. - Definitely.
(Jae Seok is the 1st to reach Course 3.)
This course is quite high and long.
There's something.
What's that?
(An oasis on the exhausting hiking trail)
Is it a drink?
(Icy soda to quench their thirst)
It's so hot.
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty too.
(Soda)
Soda?
(Panting)
(Will he be able to resist this temptation?)
(He picks up a cup?)
(Hesitant)
(Is he really going to drink the soda like this?)
What's that?
(Just then, Jong Kook joins them.)
It's a soda.
If I drank it now, it would feel so refreshing.
Will you have some? What are you going to do?
(The unbearable temptation of soda)
But if I drink this now...
I'm seriously craving it now.
(While they hesitate in front of it...)
- Are you craving it? - I'm thirsty.
(Even the slowpokes have arrived.)
- We didn't eat anything. - Okay.
- Does it have ice in it? - Let me see.
(Irresistible)
- It has ice in it. - Does it?
- It must be cool. - Really?
This is driving me crazy.
If I drink this, my thirst will be...
completely quenched.
We can mix this together.
(Kyung Hwan already grabbed the soda.)
Did you drink it?
- Are you drinking it? - Are you drinking it?
- Will you drink it? - That's...
All right. Is there anyone...
who wants to battle me?
(Tempted)
(The sweet, fizzy punch of soda tickles right up to their nose.)
- This is amazing. - I'm thirsty.
Will you leave me standing like this, all awkward?
(Tranced by the temptation, they grab their cups one by one.)
- Here. - Let's just go.
- I can pass on this. - No.
- Let's go. - No.
(The lead group, free of desires, departs without a second thought.)
- Grab one each. - Are you serious?
- Ye Eun. - Are you all drinking it?
- You don't have to force yourself. - Can I get some ice with this?
- Ye Eun, just go up. - Yes?
This isn't good for your health.
Come on, Seok Jin.
Dad! This is even worse for your health.
I didn't give birth to you.
- Your health is important. - I'm not your dad.
- You're the same age as my dad. - That's not true.
(Ddochi, who only wants iced americano, resists the soda.)
- He's older than I am. - You're Chungju Jee.
- Seok Jin, how... - All right.
(Without a care, they get ready to toast.)
You should make a toast.
- Let's eat whatever we want. - Let's eat!
Let's eat whatever we want!
Let's eat whatever we want.
(Seok Jin, Kyung Hwan, and Haha choose soda instead of the coin.)
Ye Eun, you have to drink this.
But this is...
Could you fill my cup with ice?
(Coins gained in Course 3)
This is the best-tasting soda I've ever had in my life.
- It's great. - It's really good.
- It's unbelievable. - It's amazing.
(A taste worth the coin)
Should I have one more cup?
I didn't drink it.
- You didn't? - Seriously?
(During the "Let's eat whatever we want" toast,)
Let's eat whatever we want.
(Ssaebssaeb refused to take a sip alone.)
- I'm not drinking it. - My goodness.
- I knew it. - Let's go.
(Se Chan and Ye Eun also get coins.)
- We should get the coin first. - Come here. Let's go.
- He's a total Ssaebssaeb. - We should get the coin first.
(Total coins gained: 21 out of 25)
I knew it.
You're a variety show master.
- This is the best soda I've tried. - Ye Eun, seriously...
(In the end, only Seok Jin, Haha, and Kyung Hwan...)
- Come here. - You'll be really surprised.
(fell for the temptation.)
- They drank it! - Jae Seok!
(Loudly)
We have betrayers!
This is Chapter Three.
Don't do what everyone else is doing.
- Just as expected. - You need to throw in a twist.
You're a variety show master.
They drank it, Jae Seok!
This is... I don't need a soda.
(The variety show master and disciple only want coffee.)
- I want coffee. - We have to drink coffee.
I have three coins, right?
Well...
What did the future bride say when he saw the episode?
Your future bride.
- He's my future groom. - Right, groom.
I'm the future bride. My boyfriend's the future groom.
- What did he say? - My boyfriend?
(Her old fling wants to know the gossip.)
He said it was cute.
Se Chan. I hope you meet someone nice.
(Laughing out loud)
(While Ddochi and Mr. Catfish clown around...)
Don't you worry about me.
(The lead pack reaches Course 4.)
This stage...
Is this the last stage?
It looks like it.
(What will the last supply station be?)
- Should we count... - This stage...
I want an Americano.
(It's the iced Americano they wanted so much.)
I want a cold Americano.
Let's have coffee. I want coffee.
I'm weak when it comes to coffee.
Let's make this count.
- How many do we have? - We need four.
(They immediately start to calculate the coins.)
We get three if we don't drink this.
(Total coins gained: 21 out of 25)
- Hang on. Three... - We need twenty-five coins.
- Jae Seok. - What?
(Se Chan and Ye Eun also arrive.)
- Us two. - Yes.
We're honest people.
Seok Jin and Kyung Hwan, honestly today...
They need to be punished.
(The "Let's eat whatever we want" team is still drinking their soda.)
Gosh, the ice...
- Well... - What? So what?
- What? - They're fools for skipping this.
(Self-justification)
- Yes. - See? There's coffee.
(Coffee)
He's right.
- How many do we have? - We need 25 coins.
(Heading straight forward)
I want one.
- This one... - Can we have one each?
(Coins gained in Course 4)
Some of us need to skip.
(They currently have 21 coins.)
- Why? - Those three had a soda.
Four times eight is thirty-two.
(At least 4 of them need to get coins in order to succeed.)
- Minus those three, we're at... - That's not good.
Ye Eun, you can have one.
- Go ahead. - I don't dare.
(She refuses first.)
Go ahead.
- You're desperate. - But you...
- Let the desperate drink. - Take one.
- Let's make the show work. - Do as you're told.
(Variety Shows Chapter 4: Do what you are told to do.)
Take one each.
- I'll obey my senior. - Yes.
- What about me? - You're desperate.
- I'll drink one. - Yes, go ahead.
You didn't take anything so far?
(The variety show master and disciple decide to drink.)
- I skipped all three. - Go.
- Then drink. - Go ahead.
You two can drink.
How many is it now, then?
(Groaning gasp)
- Is it nice? - It's great.
- It's tasty? - It's great!
(A long sip)
We need three, right?
(A proper caffeine fix!)
- This is insane. - Is it refreshing?
I can feel the caffeine.
This is seriously good.
(It tastes even better after the hike.)
It's so sweet.
(While they taste paradise in a cup...)
Seok Jin. Speak up today. Please.
- Okay. - Stand up against Jae Seok.
- Yes. - About what?
(They are busy encouraging the worn-out big brother.)
You want me to take on the guy with crooked teeth?
(Acting tough)
- Yes. You should... - I'll put him in his place.
- Crooked Yu. - Can you guys...
- back me up? - You bet.
(They form "Seok Sam and the Subordinates.")
To be honest,
I think you made Jae Seok what he is now.
You're not entirely wrong.
And he wants us to gather round at 2am?
I hate it when you shake your leg out of anxiety...
- when he does that. - I wasn't anxious.
(Getting defensive)
- You were. - It's a habit of mine.
- "I'm anxious." - You used to...
(Sneaking in a comment)
This isn't right.
- No. - Now that I have backup...
- Don't you worry. - Okay.
(Junior Jee is fired up.)
That punk...
(He decides to rebel.)
I'm getting more annoyed now.
Seok Jin. Tell him to meet you at 1am.
(Putting in firewood)
- That's a good idea. - You drank a soda?
What did you say?
(Loudly)
- Did you have a soda? - What do you care?
(A strange habit)
- Yes. That's the spirit. - Good.
(Chuckling)
- Was that okay? - Yes.
(Proud)
That was awesome.
Why do you care? It's my life.
- Oh, good one. - "It's my life"?
- This won't do. Guys. - Yes?
(Junior Jee gets bold with his crew backing him up.)
He needs a talking to.
I'll put some sense into you. Today's the day.
(But they shut their mouths in front of Jae Seok.)
Everyone after the seventh term, gather round.
- You... - "Gather round"? No, thanks.
Gather round. Tenth term, what?
- Seventh term? - When did you join?
Who cares about that? How long will you drag this on?
(Ear grab)
I don't believe this.
(Senior Yu immediately restores order.)
- What... - How dare you?
(Insubordination)
- Insubordination? - No.
His pinch was too weak.
Here's some insubordination for you.
(His grip is pitifully weak.)
Is this allowed?
It's not insubordination.
(Whatever.)
- How many coins so far? - Let's add it up.
(He stops Junior Jee's lesson for the mission.)
Let's do some counting.
- How many so far? - Two more can have a coffee.
(To succeed in the mission)
- Two more? - I want one.
- This is it. - Just two...
- I want one. - Just two...
- Seok Jin. - I'll have one.
(Junior Jee goes off on his own without consulting them.)
- An iced Americano? - Wait.
- You had a soda. - What?
- How many coins do you have? - I have two.
- Then don't drink. - Hey.
- You had a soda too. - Come on.
- We need to secure the center slot. - You can't have it.
(Mount Soi Observatory, Private room 1)
(It's an important chance to get the middle slot.)
- Hey. - Yes.
Can't I drink what I want to?
(Rebellious)
- Seok Jin, we... - Hey.
(Grabbing)
So what if you're our senior?
- You're a guest. - What?
- Hey. - Don't you respect guests?
(With Boss Jee acting up, his crew hesitantly joins in.)
- Guys. You won't speak up? - What?
- We need to secure the center slot. - You won't speak up?
(If all 3 of them drink, they will fail the mission!)
- Who's in the wrong? - What?
I feel like changing my mind.
What got into you?
(Seok Sam acts out to get back at Senior Yu.)
- To be honest... - Yes.
I decided on a new motto when we started the hike.
(Rebellion is quelled.)
- He took a sip. - He drank mine.
(Seok Jin uses 1 coin.)
- Seok Jin, you don't get a coin. - Why not?
- That's not fair. - Give it back.
(Why now?)
You enjoyed it. You took a long sip.
This is a mission.
We need to succeed.
(Absurd)
Let's eat what we want. That's my motto.
- Sure. - That's all good.
- This... - Eat what you want,
and depart this world first.
- That's fine. - Why would you curse me like that?
(Choking up)
Telling me to die.
- How is that a curse? - It is.
- I'm looking out for you. - It's not?
You can't eat everything you want.
You only look out for me at times like this!
I'm older, so cancel the 2am summon.
- The 2am... - Don't fight.
(Laughing)
- Cancel it. - The summon...
(He must have felt bad...)
- That's your demand? - Don't demand he cancel.
- Just don't show up. - That's it?
- Don't go. - You were...
stressed out all this while.
- Okay. It's canceled. - It's off.
I'll call it off.
(He officially cancels the 2am summon.)
I think we should let Seok Jin do whatever he wants today.
(Starting again)
- Let him eat. - Yes.
- Let us live and do what we want. - Seriously.
- We need 25 coins. - Yes.
(Total coins gained: 21 out of 25)
(They will succeed if 4 of them can hold out a little longer.)
You have 2? There's 1 more stage.
- One more to go. - Just don't.
- Hey. - What?
(At that moment...)
(A car suddenly barges in.)
Hey, this is...
What's this?
- What's that? - We have iced water...
- and air conditioning. - We get a lift?
(Iced water, air conditioning, and a ride to the top)
You can get in.
For how many coins?
(Tempted)
This is crazy.
(Running forward)
For how many coins?
- What are you doing? - What?
(The ultimate temptation came at the very end.)
- Come on. - Seok Jin.
(Seok Sam is already wavering.)
- What? - What are you doing?
How many coins for a ride?
You can get in for just one coin.
(They can get in for 1 coin.)
- Just one? - There's AC and iced water.
- We need this slot. - Haha.
(It's hard to resist, due to the heat and uphill climb.)
- Hey. - Why you...
I feel rotten now.
- Power! - Speed!
(Power and Speed are about to get in.)
- Cross! - Cross!
Don't you dare get in.
Get in and watch what happens for the rest of the day.
Who do you think you are?
- You... - You were so cool just now.
Right? Wasn't I cool?
(Proud)
(Luring with iced water)
Go. Get in.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors and get in.
- Let's take the car. For two... - Three here...
We don't know what's at the top.
(They will fail the mission if they both use their coins.)
Right. We should save up.
Why do we have to...
- coddle them? - Right.
- Why should we... - Just three people...
You're old enough to know reason.
(This is irritating.)
- Why should we... - Yes.
Let's dump him when he's of no use to us.
- Shall we do that? - Punish him then.
- Then... - Show him how we feel.
- For now... - Hang on.
(A chilling warning of exclusion)
- You'll exile him later? - Yes.
- You'll get left behind. - At the top...
No one's taking the car?
(The hand of temptation)
- No. - No takers?
- Well... - No.
(Stern)
- Let's keep climbing. - Let's go.
(He takes some coffee first.)
- Let's go. - Let's press on.
- I want a ride. - Let's go.
- You're allowed. - There's one stage left, right?
(Reading the room)
Come on now.
(The two are constantly looking for a chance to spend their coins.)
Help out the guest.
This isn't a group mission. We're fending for ourselves.
(They will fail if both get in the car.)
(The lead pack walks on, totally clueless.)
If it's cup noodles, I'll go for it.
I haven't been here in a long time.
Mount Soi Observatory.
This used to be a US Army barracks.
- What? - The building to your right.
(A Korean War US radar base)
- Oh, this one? - Yes.
I came here before you did.
(He shows off, since he has experience with Mount Soi.)
- You already know? Okay. - Yes.
There's a staircase?
I can't quit soccer even though I struggle during Running Man.
(These stairs pose a threat even to Kim Muscles.)
(The man with lean muscles leads the group in the climb.)
I should've worn a short-sleeved shirt.
Hello.
(A sweaty 40-minute climb without a break)
What's this?
Welcome to the peak.
(He finally arrived at the top.)
- Put your coins in the box. - Okay.
You made it to the top on foot,
so you get the Cheorwon specialty, Rushmelon.
(To celebrate finishing the hike,)
(they are given Cheorwon's specialty, Rushmellow.)
I want this so much.
(A cold and sweet piece of melon to chase away the sweat)
(Kook is the next to arrive.)
It's so good.
- It's so good. - Oh, mangoes.
- Melons. - Melons? Right, melons.
(He takes the free food, totally wiped out.)
- This is for free? - Yes.
For real?
Are you serious? We get a treat?
(They reach the peak one by one.)
Wait. Is this a gift?
- I want a ride. - Let's be honest.
(These two are still fighting in front of the car.)
I come on the show once a year.
I'm getting in. Let's hitch a ride together.
There must be something else.
(Total coins gained: 24 out of 25)
(They will fail the mission once two of them get in.)
But what... Why?
Let's get in.
Put your hand right here.
(Exclaiming about the cool air)
(Groaning)
Shouldn't you get out to talk to us?
Why is he staying inside?
(Displeased at the lack of effort)
You're taking the easy route.
This is the center slot of the board.
(Mount Soi Observatory, Private room 1)
- That's why... - It's a tough choice.
(In great anguish)
I don't fear getting yelled at.
- But I fear losing the center... - This is insane.
and ending up not eating lunch.
I'll walk up. You hitch a ride...
and show us how great you are.
- I can... - I want to...
- retaliate a bit. - Yes. You retaliate.
Kyung Hwan isn't here yet?
Haha's the problem. He's a troublemaker.
(They will fail the mission if both of them got in the car.)
Haha's the problem.
(Did they ride the car?)
- What are you eating? - He's here.
(At that moment)
He's here.
(Kyung Hwan walked up...)
(and so did Haha!)
It's beautiful.
Yes. You retaliate.
(After a long squabble)
- Enjoy the ride. - It's annoying.
I'll walk fast.
(Kyung Hwan gave up the ride.)
Where are you going?
(Haha follows because he doesn't want to get yelled at alone.)
- Hand over your coins. - I did.
(And so, they got 2 extra coins.)
You collected...
a total of 26 coins, so this mission is a success.
- Okay! - Okay.
Do you see the golden yellow field?
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Below Mount Soi's summit,)
- No way. - No way.
(they can see a panoramic autumn view of Cheorwon.)
It's so pretty.
It's been a while since I visited such a place.
It's so nice up here.
(The tough climb was totally worth it.)
It's just fantastic.
You cleared this mission.
Peel off the sticker that says "Mount Soi Observatory."
- Okay. - We get something.
(They open the bingo slot.)
- The private room. - The center slot...
- is important. - A private room is great.
- We won? - We got it?
- Oh, dear. - What's this?
- What's this? - It's Seok Jin's?
He gets locked up in a private room?
Seok Jin is the hidden member...
- of Mount Soi Observatory. - What now?
- It means Seok Jin gets a penalty. - What?
A penalty?
That's a bad thing, then.
(Clapping)
What?
- For doing nothing? - A penalty?
(Speechless)
- What did he do wrong? - Think about it.
What did he do wrong?
Why should anyone be penalized?
- Why... - What are you up to?
(Outraged to hear about the penalty after succeeding in the mission)
Filming crew. What are you thinking?
- I love it. - Yes.
Isn't this great?
(Senior Yu is excited to hear about Seok Sam's penalty.)
He deserves a penalty.
He always manages to escape getting penalized.
(For 6 weeks in a row)
He acted extra weird the whole climb.
What's the penalty?
- What's the reason? - Having a room is always nice.
Just like Seok Jin, who just got a penalty,
(How we choose who gets today's penalty)
the member whose face is shown...
will receive a penalty, whether or not you pass the mission.
A total of three members will get a penalty,
chosen by drawing lots from those...
(If 4 or more faces are revealed because of a failed bingo,)
who had their faces revealed.
(3 of them will be selected to receive the penalty.)
- Hold on. - It's not settled yet.
- Nothing's settled yet. - Hang on a second.
During the meeting, you already decided...
(When the production team was in a meeting)
that I was going to receive a penalty.
- No way. - Everyone always goes...
(Upset)
for the center bingo square.
- Wait. - This is bingo.
(The prime spot everyone fights for in bingo)
Even a fool goes for that square.
- That's true. - We could've failed the mission.
If it were these squares... What?
(If 4 or more squares are revealed due to a failed mission,)
- We could've failed the mission. - We almost failed.
- We barely made it this round. - Exactly.
(his penalty may be waived.)
As if they'd let us fail the mission for the center square.
(He's upset that he's in the center.)
Just so you know, it was Director Kang Chan Hee...
who assigned the squares.
- Hold on. - Chan Hee's older than you.
Chan Hee, are you kidding me?
(In advance, Chan Hee decided who went in the center.)
Seok Jin's a guy we can rely on and he's the oldest,
so he goes in the center.
(Placed in the middle hoping he'd take the penalty in stride)
Chan Hee, are you kidding me?
Wait. Chan Hee didn't come up all the way here.
He didn't join us. He's still at the bottom.
He stayed where we started.
- Chan Hee's unbelievable. - That's a 30-year veteran for you.
(He will raise his objections after coming back down.)
You completed the mission at Mount Soi Observatory.
Please go ahead and choose the next square.
(He chooses the next slot.)
- Which one should we choose? - Don't reveal it just yet.
- Jae Seok, there are two. - We should go to both.
(2 restaurants for those who are hungry)
There are two restaurants.
- Right. - One at the bottom.
- That's right. - This one.
Let's go with this one. One ondol room.
(He chooses a restaurant with an ondol room.)
We can all sleep on the ondol floor.
- Hold on. Let's do this. - It's a good room for us all.
- What are you doing? - Like this.
(A "success" sticker is placed.)
- It shows our success. - Nice.
- Right? - You’re really good.
- We should make that clear. - Are you a staff member?
- Are you a staff member? - I was picking up the slack.
- I see. - Nice work, Kyung Hwan.
(A worker who finds things to do on his own)
- There. - If we fail...
If I had known, I would've made sure we failed.
(Worked up)
- I'm going to run wild now. - Exactly.
- Seok Sam, hold on. - What?
How can you want to ruin us when the game's not over yet?
- Put yourself in my shoes. - Are you a villain?
Just imagine your face being up here instead.
What if it was your face up here?
Are you playing the villain?
Who'd want to continue with filming today?
(Annoyed)
(He's freaking out because he's been chosen for the penalty for now.)
- He's not wrong. - I'll get the penalty for sure.
If we get injured while playing today,
don't we get automatically excluded?
- He'll be like a free agent. - It's like...
- Right? Yes? - Jong Kook.
Are you thinking of snapping the leg of a swallow?
(Chills)
- Like that? - If he were injured...
I won't get injured.
I won't get injured, you punk.
(Elbow jab)
- Is this allowed? - I won't get injured.
(Elbowing the cheekbone)
You punk.
- He hit me, but it was so soft. - I mean...
Why did no one grab me?
Why is your elbow so soft?
(They head to the next location with the grumbling swallow.)
- Unbelievable. - We should get going.
- We should get going for now. - Should we move out?
- Let's go. - Let's go!
Haha, the concert was so much fun.
I had a blast.
- I loved the guest performers. - Ddochi, we could also...
hold a concert.
Ye Eun will be an asset. She can even play the piano.
(Ye Eun used to played the piano for the church service.)
- Yes, I can play it well. - You're right.
- What about us? - Ji Hyo, why don't we do something?
How about we go live and have some drinks?
- Drinks? - He's booking everyone he knows.
He's looking for guests rather than doing it on his own.
(A solo artist who isn't confident performing alone)
Why do you always need someone to join you?
(Persistent)
- It should be "Haha and Friends." - Haha, stop harassing...
(The title of the concert)
Sang Guk and Young Jin.
- How am I harassing them? - They're not good at dancing,
but you bring them along so you can look good.
(He dragged the people with no energy on stage.)
You set two poor dancers beside you.
- You saw them work hard, right? - It's just to make him look good.
They were so intimidated because Jae Seok would be there too.
- Were they intimidated? - Totally.
Why are people intimidated by Jae Seok's presence?
I just don't get it. Why?
You're intimidated by him too.
What do you mean I'm intimidated?
You were shaking your legs when we were called in at 2am.
(He told everyone to gather.)
No way.
- Also... - What?
- Can I talk? - You were shaking your legs.
- No way. You've got it wrong. - Hold on.
(Tapping)
- Kyung Hwan... - Stop poking me!
- Kyung Hwan's trying to talk. - Don't touch me.
(Warning him without being able to look at him)
Stop poking me.
My eyes...
- Look at him. - Don't touch my glasses. Don't.
(Senior Yu freely puts his fingers in and out of his glasses.)
- This is funny. - I might explode.
- This is funny. - Don't touch them.
(Jeehuahua can't shake him off, so he's just shouting.)
Don't pull on my ears.
Don't touch my hat. Just don't.
- This is funny. - I've warned you.
(He looks like a mess.)
Just don't.
(Ending with a weak warning)
That was funny.
- Kyung Hwan was talking to you. - That's so funny.
Unbelievable. I need to teach him a lesson.
(Laughing)
Kyung Hwan hasn't been able to say a word. Are you okay?
- Why would you address that? - I mean...
He hasn't been able to say anything. Are you good?
He's not a professional, so...
He falls somewhere between a pro and an amateur.
That's why I'm here for a two-day event.
- I have so much time left. - There's a lot of time left.
(Relaxed)
- Of course. - That's why you're not anxious.
(He still has plenty of time before his deadline.)
- He hadn't been saying anything. - I'll get up...
at three in the morning and talk alone.
- Is that a waterfall? - No way.
- There's a waterfall here. - It's so pretty.
(A breathtaking waterfall view unfolds...)
There's a restaurant off to its side.
What a view, right?
(in front of the restaurant.)
(You can enjoy the refreshing sound of rushing water...)
The river is running high.
- That's so cool. - Nice.
(and the cool spray of waterfall as an appetizer.)
You've arrived at the restaurant you chose.
(Even the scenery is delicious at the first restaurant.)
Known for its scenic location right next to Jiktang Waterfall,
it also serves fantastic spicy fish stew.
- Spicy fish stew! - Mandarin fish stew sounds good.
We picked a good one.
First, we'll reveal who occupies the penalty square for this round.
- Do we reveal it first? - That first?
- It's either me or Ye Eun. - That first?
(Mr. Free Meals)
Don't you think it'll be me or Jae Seok?
- This time... - I think it'll be me.
(The Free Meals Couple is nervous about getting the restaurant slot.)
- Food is involved. - It'll be me since we're eating.
Reveal it.
(Whose photo is in the restaurant slot?)
It could be Haha.
- What? - It's Kyung Hwan.
(Heo Kyung Hwan)
(Shouting)
- Heo Kyung Hwan. - It's Heo Kyung Hwan.
(Kyung Hwan will receive a penalty.)
- Heo Kyung Hwan. - Let's do our best.
(Cheering)
Since Kyung Hwan's face was revealed,
- he's up for the penalty. - Sure.
For this round, you'll go one at a time.
- What? - It must be a group thing.
Jae Seok, you'll go first.
(Jae Seok gets off the bus 1st.)
- Do we have to choose something? - What's going on?
- Jae Seok... - Go with the one on the right.
- Jae Seok, remember our vibe. - Okay.
(Jae Seok is the first one to get off the bus.)
- This... - Stay true to yourself.
This place is just...
(Impressed)
Check out this scenery.
(What's the mission that'll win them the spicy fish stew?)
What? No way.
(Two pots of spicy fish stew?)
All right. This game is called...
Unanimous Toppings.
That looks so good.
Between handmade sujebi and ramyeon noodles,
choose the topping you want in your spicy fish stew.
What?
You win if you all choose the same one...
- and will get to enjoy the stew. - How can we possibly succeed?
My gosh.
(It's like choosing between Mom and Dad.)
I love them both. Can't I choose both?
No, you can only choose one.
No way.
Can't I taste it?
- Just a taste? - Yes.
We'll give you a spoon.
(His sheer desperation earned him a taste.)
Who knew they'd be such a beautiful waterfall?
(Stunning scenery that only enhances the stew's flavor)
This place is incredible.
You'll all get a chance to taste it.
(Anticipating)
- Really? - Then, you'll choose.
(Gasping)
(Perfectly cooked noodles...)
(drenched in the stew broth)
This is what I absolutely love.
(Slurping)
(Slurping up noodles to fill his mouth)
(Bouncy noodles with a waterfall of umami)
(Eyes widening)
It's so good.
Now this.
(He tries the handmade sujebi next.)
These chopsticks are clean.
(Plump)
It's so good.
(This time, the chewiness comes crashing in.)
Please choose your topping.
(Ramyeon noodles or handmade sujebi, what's Jae Seok's choice?)
This is a tough one.
But I'll always choose ramyeon noodles.
- Ramyeon noodles? - Yes.
(He hesitated for a moment, but chose ramyeon.)
- Got it. - But...
we have to eat this. We just have to.
(Worried)
(Se Chan's next.)
Handmade sujebi is the right topping for spicy fish stew.
(Sujebe is the go-to choice for the spicy fish stew.)
But you made Jae Seok choose first.
(Jae Seok is crazy about ramyeon.)
I know what Jae Seok likes.
To get a unanimous vote,
we'll stick to what Jae Seok likes and go with ramyeon.
Today, we're voting unanimously for the ramyeon noodles.
(Se Chan knows what his friend likes and chooses ramyeon!)
(Ye Eun is next.)
What's this?
- The game is Unanimous Toppings. - This is crazy.
This looks so good.
(Mouthwatering)
I bet everyone chose ramyeon noodles.
Jae Seok probably chose that.
Handmade sujebi is what I want.
(Contemplating)
Oh, no. Do I go with ramyeon noodles?
But this is what I want.
(Ramyeon noodles or handmade sujebi, Food Fighter's ultimate dilemma)
- I'll get you a tray. - Please take your bowl with you.
(She makes her choice after some thought.)
My gosh. Look at that.
(Next is Seok Jin.)
Jae Seok would've chosen the noodles for sure.
But I want the sujebi.
(Handmade sujebi in the spicy fish stew is irresistible.)
You can have ramyeon noodles all the time, but sujebi...
These were rolled out by hand.
(Chewy handmade sujebi)
Where else could you eat this?
Unbelievable.
(Which one did Seok Sam choose?)
I just hope I chose the right answer.
(She's contemplating as well.)
What do I do?
No wonder people took a while.
(Upset)
This is a tough choice.
Why can't I take my eyes off the sujebi?
(Bouncy)
The members all love ramyeon noodles but...
(Ramyeon is their comfort food,)
(but sujebi goes with the stew.)
The right choice should be sujebi.
- This is what I want. - Jae Seok already chose, right?
(Will they make a unanimous choice?)
- We've talked about ramyeon a lot. - Then ramyeon it is.
I feel bad for the staff today.
- Wasn't it too easy? - It was.
(The members made their choices.)
See? That's what 16 years of teamwork looks like.
If someone answered wrong...
(Everyone seems to believe they chose the same thing.)
But Kyung Hwan's here.
- Kyung Hwan... - His face was revealed.
If we get a bingo, Kyung Hwan has to take the penalty.
If Kyung Hwan ruins this for us,
(They're not sure about Kyung Hwan.)
nobody is going to play fair anymore.
Then it's total war. I'm going to sabotage too.
(What will Kyung Hwan choose since he's up for a penalty?)
To be honest, I love sujebi.
(Thinking hard)
But the ramyeon noodles?
- If we fail this mission, - Yes?
doesn't that cancel out my penalty?
Okay, I'll choose. Here we go.
(Kyung Hwan, who's likely to get a penalty, made his choice.)
This was too easy.
(Will they make a unanimous choice?)
I could've done it with my eyes closed.
- This... - Kyung Hwan, was this easy or not?
- It was so easy. - Well,
- the answer was clear. - There was one clear answer.
- Exactly. - Of course.
- It was the easiest game ever. - This was the easiest game...
(They say it was easy to choose.)
- in the history of unanimous votes. - The easiest!
- There's one clear answer. - There's no way.
(Did they set their differences aside and make the same choice?)
- It was too easy. - Okay, we'll start with Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok will reveal what he chose first.)
- All right. One, two... - This was too easy.
- Ramyeon noodles. - Ramyeon noodles!
- Who here didn't choose that? - That was the clear answer.
With me playing, it'll always be the noodles.
(He still chose ramyeon for the spicy fish stew.)
- Jong Kook, go ahead. - One, two, three.
(Next is Jong Kook.)
- Ramyeon noodles. - Of course.
(He chose ramyeon.)
- This was too easy. - Of course this was what I chose.
- Se Chan, go ahead. - Too easy. One, two, three.
(Next is Se Chan.)
(He chose ramyeon.)
- Ramyeon noodles. - Nice.
- Too easy. - Come on.
- Seok Jin... - Let's see what Haha chose.
- Maybe Seok Jin went rogue. - You never know.
- It's over. - Sixteen years of Running Man.
We're together, ramyeon.
- Right. It's ramyeon. - Of course.
(So far, it's unanimously ramyeon.)
Of course.
Haha loves Running Man so much.
- Easy. - Kyung Hwan.
(But next is Kyung Hwan, and they weren't sure about his choice.)
Everyone.
It was such an easy game.
(What did Kyung Hwan pick?)
Sujebi...
(He picked sujebi.)
You failed to make a unanimous decision.
Kyung Hwan.
(Boiling with rage)
Do you think I'm the only one who picked sujebi?
Why did you pick sujebi?
(They failed to make a unanimous choice.)
- He... - You don't know Running Man.
- He doesn't suit Running Man. - He...
- You're not fit for this. - Just do "Hangout with Yoo."
- It's not that I don't fit here. - You don't fit.
(The culprit behind the failure makes his defense.)
Let me be honest.
- He really doesn't fit. - For me,
- the penalty is at stake. - No.
I don't really need...
(They worried he might try to avoid the penalty.)
to succeed in the mission, right?
We can go horizontally too.
(Bingo)
I like sujebi.
But I think it's this one.
Still, I'll go with sujebi.
He went with a different one.
(He picked sujebi to get out of the penalty.)
I knew he would go with a different one.
It's going to be war later.
- This is really... - Seriously.
I'm sure there's another person who picked sujebi.
- No. - If I'm wrong,
(Did any of the three remaining members pick sujebi?)
- I'll... - There will be no more.
If you end up being the only one who picked sujebi,
- I won't forgive you. - If I'm wrong,
- I'll jump into the water. - Nice.
If you're the only one who picked sujebi, you're going into the water.
You'll go into the water.
(If he's the only one who picked sujebi,)
(he'll jump into Hantan River.)
The water...
(Laughing)
- You're jumping into the water. - If it's just Kyung Hwan...
Why are you laughing?
If you're the only one who picked sujebi, you're going into the water.
(What did the remaining members choose?)
You'll go into the water.
- Let's see what Ye Eun picked. - Ye Eun.
(Ye Eun will reveal her choice.)
Of course, I picked...
One, two...
(Kyeon Hwan's fate rests on her choice. What did she pick?)
Ye Eun would know.
- Sujebi. - Sujebi! See? It's there.
(She chose sujebi.)
- Don't you... - She's...
- Don't you... - Ye Eun...
(Disappointed)
- Hey. - You were the third person...
(His prediction was spot on.)
Listen to me.
- Hey. - I knew Jae Seok'd pick ramyeon.
You like "Saturday Night Live Korea," right?
I picked ramyeon at first.
- Office workers? - Let's check Ji Hyo's.
- It looked so good. - Let's see.
(The sujebi looks so good.)
You shouldn't be shaken by that.
(The mouthwatering sujebi clouded her judgment.)
The answer was obvious.
- Let's check Ji Hyo's. - It looked so good.
- See what the original member did. - Right.
- Right. - Original member.
(Ji Hyo, the original member, will reveal her choice.)
She knows all the members.
- Sixteen years. - She knows everyone. Sixteen years.
- It's been 16 years. - I...
- One, two, three! - I...
- picked sujebi. - Sujebi!
(Cheering)
Seriously.
- Sujebi! - Seriously.
(She chose sujebi, the unwritten rule for spicy fish stew.)
Goodness, Ji Hyo!
It's been 16 years!
(Deeply disappointed)
- I'm really... - I thought...
- about picking ramyeon. - Ji Hyo!
(Even the original member couldn't resist sujebi.)
- The answer was given. - You should have picked ramyeon.
- Let's check Seok Sam's. - The eldest brother.
(Lastly)
- It's the eldest brother. - The eldest brother.
Sixteen years...
Just look at it. There.
Let's check.
- Why would you need to check? - Come on.
(Seok Sam also picked sujebi.)
Seriously.
Come on.
- Everyone is staying behind today. - See?
- At what time? - We have to stay behind.
We have to gather up. Let's meet at 12:30am.
We're meeting at 12:30am.
(The assembly time is announced again.)
He's shaking his legs again.
(PTSD from being called to assemble)
We're meeting at 12:30am.
(Nervous)
You failed to make a unanimous decision.
No meal will be served.
(They narrowly missed out on the spicy fish stew.)
- What? - Seriously.
You failed the bingo as well.
(Sad)
That's why...
- Come on. - We should eat first.
We have to go to a restaurant again.
(They failed to get bingo.)
We have to go to a restaurant.
Let's go. We have to go.
(They head to the next restaurant.)
- We can go diagonally. - Seriously.
How can we come here...
- and not eat this? - I know, right?
(They couldn't have spicy fish stew because of their weak teamwork.)
We're leaving without getting to try this.
How could you not pick ramyeon?
- It's shocking. - This is more...
If you take off your cap...
- Seriously. - Today...
It's the biggest shock of the year.
- You decided to twist things? Okay. - Today, we....
(Despite all the time they spent together,)
- I'm really... - It was such a great dish.
(some of them still chose sujebi.)
How could you not pick ramyeon...
- in Running Man? - I mean...
I would understand if someone else had gone first.
- But Jae Seok went first. - Right.
(The ramyeon lover's choice wasn't unexpected.)
- You would know what he chose. - I was going to pick that, but...
It's such a shame.
(Feeling betrayed)
- I thought there would be a twist. - I don't think I can see them.
- It's such a shame. - You thought they'd twist things.
- Yes. - It's been 16 years.
It was those three and you.
- I thought Haha... - But you're a guest, so okay.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
You've not been here for 16 years, though.
Seriously.
- That's hurtful. - That's hurtful.
(Terribly disappointed)
That's hurtful.
It doesn't apply to you.
- That's hurtful. - That was really harsh.
Seok Jin...
- We should set things straight. - Today, I'm...
Seriously...
- That hurts a bit. - He's still...
Ssaebssaeb.
(Tapping)
- That's... - He's still...
How many years has it been for you?
- Ten years. - Ten years. Right.
Let me tell you again.
You can't say, "It's been 16 years."
- Then... - "It's been 16 years."
(Ssaebssaeb isn't allowed to talk about their 16 years together.)
It's been ten years.
"It's been ten years" is fine, right?
Ten years is fine.
(Drawing a firm line)
Goodness.
- He's strict. - Right.
- This is a bit... - Se Chan...
cares a lot about Running Man.
- No one loves it more than me. - That's right.
I monitor it every week.
"That doesn't apply to you."
That's not what I meant.
(Emotional)
I wanted to make it clear. We're a family.
Do you even know his name?
I root for his future.
- I always wish he does well, - Seok Sam.
but he's not been here for 16 years.
- It's been two years for Ye Eun. - Yes.
(And it's been 2 years for Ye Eun.)
- Seriously, today... - Two and a half years.
I made up my mind.
We're gathering at 12:30am.
(Staring into the distance)
You'll meet...
Did we really leave...
(Gloomy)
- without having fish stew? - What a shame.
- We couldn't have ramyeon. - Seriously.
(They couldn't agree on one choice.)
- It was just given to us. - I'm sorry.
Let's eat this time.
Get it together, Song Ji Hyo!
- Ji Ye Eun! - Yes.
- Heo Kyung Hwan! - Yes.
(He chose sujebi as well.)
Get it together. We have to eat this time.
- That's right. - Then listen.
Let's say we go there and see jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.
- What do we choose? - It's jjamppong!
If Jae Seok goes first, it's jjajangmyeon.
Right. If Jae Seok goes first, it's jjajangmyeon.
(They're trying to make the same choice.)
If I go first, it's jjamppong.
- If he goes first, it's jjamppong. - Jjamppong.
- What's Se Chan's pick? - Jjajangmyeon.
- Jjajangmyeon. - Spicy jjamppong.
- Se Chan would choose jjamppong. - What about you?
(Pretending to know)
- What's your pick? - I'd pick jjajangmyeon.
You'll go with jjajangmyeon?
You don't know anything about my preferences.
- What about you? - You...
I don't know so well because it's only been ten years.
- I'd know if it was 16 years. - He means it. Okay.
(6 year short, they still have a lot to learn about each other.)
He's only been here for ten years.
- He'll know my preferences... - He's the worst.
- once I fill 16 years. - He's really cold.
- He's really... - Ten years.
Shut it.
I've been here for ten years. Can't I even talk?
"Ten years, shut it."
(You've been with us only for ten years. Be quiet.)
- Seriously. - Ten years...
- I feel intimidated. - Ten years.
Ten years, shut it.
(While Ten Years is being put in line...)
What is this place?
(They arrive at the second restaurant.)
- What's acorn imja soup? - Acorn.
We've arrived at the second restaurant.
If you fail here,
you don't get lunch today.
That's...
- Was Ma Ro always like that? - We should try...
He doesn't give us food.
- Wasn't he kind? - Seriously.
- Right. - How many years have you been here?
- Haha... - It hasn't been a year yet.
(Checking the main producer's career)
- It's been five months. - Say something.
- What? - He's been here for five months.
What a small fry.
You're not going to feed us?
(He's putting Five Months in line after the no-food rule.)
Ten years...
(Will they be able to eat in this restaurant?)
- Let's go. - I'm hungry.
We should eat.
(They enter the second restaurant, clutching their growling stomachs.)
Acorn imja soup.
- This place is nice. - It looks good.
Acorn is also...
(If they fail this time, they'll have to skip lunch.)
- Acorn tastes good. - Right.
All right.
It's cool here.
What's going on? Is the air conditioner on?
It's a natural breeze.
- Natural breeze. - It's so refreshing.
(Welcomed by the crisp autumn breeze,)
This restaurant serves various dishes...
using acorns, which are in season in the fall.
It's a restaurant specializing in acorn dishes.
Acorn imja soup, which got its name...
because perilla seeds were called "imja" in "Donguibogam,"
(this place serves up a hearty spread of acorn dishes,)
and acorn tangsu is famous here.
(from acorn imja soup with sujebi...)
- Imja. - Yes.
- Imja. - We have to eat this.
(to chewy, crispy acorn tangsu, all brimming with the flavors of fall.)
That's amazing.
Before we begin the mission,
I'll reveal the penalty receiver for the restaurant slot.
Please bring in the board.
Why do I feel like it's going to be me?
(Nervous)
- Should we remove it? - Should we remove it?
We have to go for the Military Camp Training later.
(Restaurant, room with a bed 1)
- Even if it's me, - Who is it?
(Who is the 3rd candidate to receive a penalty?)
- I'll still eat. - It's about time I show up.
- Please. - Please!
- It's Ye Eun. - What?
(Ji Ye Eun)
(True to her Food Fighter reputation,)
(her photo was in the restaurant slot.)
It's Ddochi.
(Current penalty candidates: Seok Jin, Kyung Hwan, Ye Eun)
Ye Eun whose face is shown will get the penalty.
(A mission with a meal at stake)
This mission...
is No Touch Tongs Chef.
- What's that? - No Touch Tongs Chef?
You'll team up in threes and make brownies...
using all-purpose tongs instead of your hands...
- to complete the mission. - What?
- Brownies? - How do you make brownies?
You'll have eight minutes.
You have just one chance to successfully make the brownies.
- How do you make brownies? - You fail if you spill...
(Fail)
all the ingredients or the brownies are inedible.
You'll succeed if you put them into the microwave...
within eight minutes.
(Success)
- Without using our hands? - Yes. We'll give you tongs.
(He can't believe what he heard.)
(They can only cook with tongs.)
- We have to mix the dough? - Yes.
You only have one chance,
so please pick three of your best members.
Who's going to do the baking?
You'll need a good sense of balance.
Will you go, Kyung Hwan?
(They get the recipe to choose the best members to cook.)
- Here. - We shouldn't spill them.
But brownies...
(Everyone checks the recipe.)
wouldn't be so hard to make.
Okay, 400g of brownie mix.
(Brownie recipe)
(1. Add the brownie mix, cooking oil, and 3 eggs to a bowl.)
(2. Mix until all the lumps are gone.)
(1. Ingredient prep that requires careful attention to detail)
Three eggs, cooking oil...
We need to mix well until all the lumps are gone.
(2. Kneading that requires strength and grip)
Should I do this?
- We can't use our hands. - They'll give us tongs.
(3. Transferring the sticky batter)
- We're going to use tongs. - We're going to use tongs.
We have to use the tongs well.
(4. Use tongs to open the microwave!)
I understood.
- That's... - How are we going to crack...
the eggs? We should also...
Ssaebssaeb should do that.
(Ssaebssaeb is nimble.)
- Without using our hands? - Ssaebssaeb should do that.
Jae Seok, Ssaebssaeb, and Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is strong,
(The human mixer Kim Muscles...)
so he'd knead it well.
Se Chan is quick with his hands.
(and the quick-handed Bucktooth Brothers are recommended.)
And Jae Seok cooks well.
I think this is going to be easy.
- I'll do it. - Ji Hyo is also good.
No.
(Calm down.)
Don't do it.
Why can't I... Ten Years...
Let Ten Years speak.
(Polite)
- Ten Years... - We have to succeed here.
So all the people...
(Let's play it safe.)
- who aren't here should do this. - Right.
We'll succeed, no matter what.
(Sulky)
You need a strong grip.
Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and you can do it.
This one.
- I think it'll need some strength. - It requires strength.
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Se Chan will cook as they're quite strong.)
- The baking itself... - A strong grip.
isn't difficult.
With these tongs?
- Yes. - You'll hold them with these?
(It takes considerable grip strength to use the long tongs.)
- How will you crack the eggs? - Even the lids...
You also have to open the lids.
This is hard.
(Jae Seok is practicing.)
The eggs...
(Heavy)
This...
Do you have to open the lids with those too?
- What about this? - I guess so.
- You have to open the lids. - Hold that.
Opening the lid is going to be hard.
(Missing)
You have to put it into the microwave in eight minutes.
(They need to have strong forearms and a solid grip.)
- It's not easy. - You have to work in pairs.
- Hold it tightly. - I'll hold it.
- Hold it tightly. - Try it.
(The three work on it together.)
- Like this? - Not...
(Opening)
- Right. That's good. - Like that?
Good.
(The three chefs need to cooperate to cook with the tongs.)
- Good. - You need a strong grip.
We picked the best members.
- We can do this... - Yes.
(Pastry chefs with brains, brawn, and flair)
Just think of yourselves as robots.
- Okay, let's go! - Let's eat!
Let's go!
(They need to complete the mission to eat lunch this time.)
- We have to eat here. - It's not so hard.
- We have to eat. - We have to eat here.
(Please)
- Ready... - All right.
(Will they be able to make a brownie?)
Okay.
(The 8-minute countdown begins.)
(1. Add the brownie mix, cooking oil, and 3 eggs to a bowl.)
- Raise it. - That's right.
We shouldn't spill it.
- Hold on. - Okay.
(Opening the brownie mix)
- You'll have to flip it over. - Good luck.
(Carefully opening the box)
- Good luck. - Hold it tight.
- You can tear it. - Tear it.
- We have to eat here. - Good. What's inside?
(Grabbing)
- Knock it over. - Grab it.
(They've changed their strategy and are trying to break it down.)
- Is there something inside? - Pull it out.
- But a game like this... - What on earth?
(It's not even easy to get the mix out.)
- What's wrong? - Pull it out.
- Don't spill anything. - Hold on.
- Do it over the bowl. - Empty it out.
(Pouty Mouth's support)
- Grab it. - What's the situation there?
Didn't you say we shouldn't dump in all the ingredients?
(Grabbing)
This isn't powder.
(Pulling out)
It's not powder.
(They need to open the plastic bag now!)
I thought that'd be a powder.
- You need to cut it with scissors. - Cut it with scissors.
- Use the scissors! - I thought that'd be a powder.
We need to use scissors.
- Jae Seok. - Rip it open.
- Use the scissors. - Place it in there first.
(They put it in a bowl.)
One, two...
(Poking)
- Rip it open. - It's powder.
- Empty it. - Hey, don't spill.
(But the hole is tiny.)
- Do it together. - You can't spill anything.
- Let's do it together. - Here.
- Let go. Good. - Rip it open.
(You guys do it.)
- Empty it. It all goes in the bowl. - Use it all.
- Make the hole bigger. - We're short on time.
(Here!)
Ten Years, 400g.
There.
(Jong Kook is digging around the small hole.)
- All of it. - Go, Ten Years.
- We got it. - Nice work.
- We ripped it open. - Get 400g.
(Trying his hardest)
Here we go.
They need to speed things up.
(Anxious)
- Right. - We're doing great.
- Work together. - We need all of this.
(He starts twisting the tongs like a drill.)
- It's hard not to jump in and help. - They got it.
- You got it. - Don't spill.
- Don't worry. - Just rip it open.
You need a strong grip.
- Here it comes. - There you go.
(Pouring)
Good job.
Ten Years is doing great.
- Get it all out. - Lower it a bit.
(Ten Years is pulling out a trick.)
Go, Ten Years.
- Ten Years, you have our vote. - Thanks.
I think that's enough.
Keep it to yourself, old man.
(He's been getting picked on for 16 years.)
- That's enough. - That's more than enough.
- It isn't. - You're wasting time.
(Ignoring, yapping)
- Dump it here. - You're good.
- There. - Are we done?
(The brownie mix is ready.)
- Are you done? - Place the wrapper here.
(They're trying to measure the cooking oil now.)
- Here. - Over here.
- Here we go. - I see.
(Grabbing the middle)
- You need 100ml of cooking oil. - I'll grab it here.
(Grabbing the bottom)
How did you even come up with this game?
There you go.
(He opens the lid right away.)
- How much? 100ml? - Half a cup.
(The correct amount is half a paper cup.)
- Jae Seok, from here... - Half a cup.
- We need half a cup. - Can you squeeze the bottle?
Hold on.
- Someone needs to squeeze it. - Yes, squeeze it for me.
- There you go! - More.
(Squeezing)
- Nice. - Once more.
- Ten Years, good idea. - See?
- Thanks for that. - More.
(Se Chan is grabbing the bottle...)
- More. - Nice.
(while Jae Seok pumps it.)
- I love it. - That's more than enough.
(Squeezing)
- No, we need half a cup. - Half a cup, so a little more.
- A little more. - A little more.
(Straining his forearm)
- Keep squeezing. - Okay, good.
- There you go. - We're good.
- Okay. - It tastes better...
with plenty of cooking oil.
(That's exactly half a cup.)
- Should I put it here? - No, not there.
- In there. - In here?
- In here. - Okay.
(The oil gets mixed into the powder.)
The eggs!
- Nice. - Can you even do this?
- Three eggs. - Three eggs.
(The remaining ingredient is 3 eggs.)
- Three eggs. - Are you sure you can get the eggs?
- Guys, like this. - Here.
(About 5 minutes are left.)
Why don't we just crack them in here?
- No. - No, don't.
(Moving)
- In here. - In the paper cup?
- Hold on. - Wait.
(Jae Seok grabbed one of the eggs.)
- Crack them in here first. - Then, let's remove the shells.
(Tapping)
- Careful. - That might drop.
(If he spills the egg, it's an instant fail.)
(He quickly transfers it to the bowl.)
- Good job. - Nicely done.
(Nice!)
- Done. - Looking good.
- Here it comes. - There you go. Nice.
He could just repeat that.
(Squeezing every last bit of strength out of his forearm)
- He's really good at this. - Throw it away here.
(You're doing great.)
- Do it again. - Do that again.
- Jae Seok, go ahead. - We need three.
(The next egg is ready.)
- All right. - We need three.
- We need three. - Nice job.
(Grabbing gently)
- Keep the bowl still. - Got it.
(He's using the long tongs as if they're his arm.)
Only 16 years of chemistry could make this happen.
- Nice. - Take your time.
(Cracking)
- Really? - Ten years wouldn't crack it.
(His lips are sticking out as he concentrates.)
We can pick out any eggshells...
- that drop in. - Okay.
Take your time.
- He's not dropping any eggshells. - Hold on.
I'll tap it from above.
(Tapping lightly)
- Looking good. - Nice.
That's 16 years of chemistry at work.
- All right. - One more.
(He has great control over the tongs.)
Here's one more. Go ahead.
- Look at Jae Seok go. - That's 16 years of chemistry.
(One egg is left.)
- No way. - Careful.
(If he cracks it successfully, all the ingredients will be ready.)
Keep the bowl steady.
- I think three minutes have passed. - That could smell.
- We have to be careful. - We could do this.
- Watch out. - Nice.
(Highly focused)
- More? - Just a little more.
Should I crack it open a bit?
(Tapping)
You got it!
(Jae Seok cracked 3 eggs!)
- Nice. - You got it.
- Nice. - Great job.
(Impressed)
Mix it all together.
(2. Mix until all the lumps are gone.)
- With this. - Let's do this. It's doable.
- Ten Years is up next. - What do we mix it with? Not that.
- With this? Wait, that? - Get mixing.
(They're trying to mix it with mini whisks.)
These look like robot arms.
- Do it together. - Doesn't it need water?
It doesn't need water.
(Struggling)
- Doesn't it need water? - This is cute.
Isn't this adorable?
- Do it together. - Together.
(Looking pathetic)
It doesn't need water.
Can't we mix it with the tongs?
- Just mix it. - Let's use this.
(He mixes it with tongs.)
- Is that it? - Should we mix with our robot arms?
- The robot arms? - Yes, the robot arms.
That's actually a good option.
(Chef Yu is picking up the pace with the tongs.)
- Yes, mix with the robot arms. - Use this.
Use the arms instead.
Someone keep the bowl steady.
(Grabbing)
- I got it. - Are they mixing with the arms?
- Who cares? - That looks like a good idea.
(Robot Jae Seok is moving his arm like a human mixer.)
Jong Kook, help out if you can.
With 2 members who have 16 years of chemistry,
(Perfect teamwork)
success is guaranteed.
- This is 16 years of chemistry. - This...
- Check out that teamwork. - Ten years...
Does stirring it really call for 16 years of chemistry?
(16 years of skill)
He's behind with just ten years.
- It smells like a brownie. - I smell it too.
- Check out that teamwork. - Ten years...
- This is crazy. - Guys, listen.
Ten Years is keeping the bowl steady.
(6 years of experience make the difference.)
- See that? - Right.
It takes 16 years to get to the stirring.
(Proud)
When do you graduate from that?
That's the difference.
He's like a viper.
(An old snake)
The difference between 16 years and...
Unbelievable.
(Feeling small)
- I'll adjust my grip. - Hold it steady.
- We're almost there. - Stir it some more.
(Mixing hard)
- More. - Jong Kook, nice job.
- Looking good. - More.
(With 3 minutes left, he switches into power mode.)
- Jong Kook, nice. - Go, Chef.
- Looking good. - We have more than enough time.
I don't see any more lumps.
(It's perfectly mixed!)
- We're good. - Aren't we good?
- Bake it now. - Use this next.
(3. Pour the batter into the pan.)
- Se Chan, grab that. Good. - This one?
- This is the tricky part. - Just pour it all out.
- Can you grab it there? - Lift it.
(They're trying to work together.)
- Lift it, and I'll... - This requires strength.
- Pour it. - You need to grab this.
- Keep it steady. - Grab that.
(Slipping)
- Hold on. - Grab it.
- Hold it tight. - It's slippery.
- Hold it tight. - Right here.
It's hard to grab the bowl.
- Really? - It's slippery.
This doesn't look easy.
(They run into trouble just when they're about to succeed.)
- If you can... - You need to lift it.
Somebody has to scrape the batter out.
- Exactly. - Scrape it out.
(Anxious)
- Wait. - This requires strength.
- This doesn't look easy. - This must be tough.
- How much time do they have left? - Hold it tight.
- Two minutes. - You have two minutes.
(Only 2 minutes are left.)
- All right. - Should we try the spoons?
Maybe we can scoop it up with paper cups.
They'll bend too easily.
Why don't you scoop it up?
(He uses a paper shovel.)
- Won't a spoon be better? - How about you use this?
- Look. - That's it.
(He scooped it!)
- Nice. - Go, Ten Years.
(Se Chan used another trick!)
- Ten Years, nice job. - That looks like jjajang sauce.
Go, Ten Years!
(I'll give you credit for that!)
Ten Years, look at you go.
- Nice. - Look at that.
(Ssaebssaeb calmly transfers the batter.)
- Nice. - Try scraping the bowl...
- with the spatula. - That's it.
Easier said than done.
- It seems easy, but... - Why you...
(Oh, no)
I just wanted to say that it's harder than it looks.
Did what I said come across as offensive?
(Mumbling)
Scrape it clean.
- Nice. We're almost done. - Hold on.
We're almost done on our end.
We'll eat for sure.
- We'll eat for sure. - How much time do we have left?
The batter turned out really well.
(They poured the last cup of batter into the pan.)
- Nice. - Looking good.
- Put it in the microwave. - Okay, let's do it.
- Open the microwave. - Are we good?
(All they have to do is put it in the microwave!)
- Yes, let's place it in there. - Let's do this.
Open the microwave.
- Open it. - The teamwork is off the charts.
(Ssaebssaeb quickly opened the microwave.)
- But... - Nice.
- Hold on. - You need to put it inside.
- Nice. - Careful. Don't spill.
(Careful)
- Hold on tight. - You need to put it inside.
- There. - Close the door.
(He put it in the microwave safely!)
- Aren't we done? - You're done.
- Okay. - Is that it?
(Operation Brownie complete.)
(The three of them showed perfect teamwork.)
- Nice! - No way.
- The eggs were the highlight. - That was awesome.
(But if they went over 8 minutes, they failed the mission.)
Let's actually cook this.
- And the result? - Sure.
(How long did it take in total?)
You were given eight minutes,
but you completed it in 7 minutes and 37 seconds.
(Mission success!)
Nice job.
- Of course we succeeded. - Ten years.
(Appealing)
We'll set this to eight minutes.
(They complete the mission and earn their lunch.)
- Sure, go ahead. - Good job, guys.
- Thanks, guys. - Okay!
(While the tong-wielding pastry chefs' brownie is baking,)
- No way. - Okay.
- The weather is amazing. - That fresh forest scent.
(they enjoy the scenery.)
This is nice.
Why don't the 16-year veterans gather to breathe in this air?
That sounds nice.
(They're really enjoying using their seniority.)
If you'd done the mission instead of Se Chan,
it would've taken just five minutes.
(He doesn't really like Ten Years.)
They took 7 minutes and 30 seconds.
You guys would've only needed five minutes.
(Staring)
- Let's not tell Se Chan that. - Of course.
What is it? Tell me.
What? It's nothing.
What did Seok Jin say?
What did Grandpa say?
- Grandpa? - If I had taken your place,
we would've only needed five minutes.
(Laughing hysterically)
(Chuckling)
(10 years after joining, he finally gets hazed.)
Seok Sam, come on.
He's hilarious.
- He's the best. - After eating,
why don't the 16-year veterans take a photo out there?
(He suggests taking a commemorative photo after 16 years.)
To celebrate our 16 years.
Sounds good.
- That'll be nice to see. - I love it.
Ten Years will take the photo for you.
(Giving up)
He's hilarious.
Before you eat,
(Before they eat, they have to choose the next slot.)
you'll choose the next bingo square.
We should go with the military camp training.
(Military Camp Training)
I can't believe we were trapped into this.
- It's 1:08pm right now. - Sure.
The military training takes two hours...
- because it includes rappelling. - Really?
If you go there after lunch, there's a good chance...
(They don't have enough time to finish their meal before leaving.)
- it'll end after 4pm. - I see.
(If it's past 4pm, they'll fail the bingo.)
- That's an automatic fail. - We should choose something else.
- Choose something else. - We'll have to go...
(Columnar Joints, Goseokjeong Flower Field)
to the columnar joints instead.
We need to head this way.
Life would've been so much easier if we'd gotten the ramyeon right.
Had we gotten that one, we'd be set up for a bingo.
(After failing the topping mission, their bingo line is up in the air.)
Tell me about it.
Considering our chances,
doing the one above is much safer.
- This one? - Yes.
(If they visit the waterfall, they'll have more choices.)
- That path is already blocked. - But...
Exactly.
We're torn between this and this.
- Yes, that's the right choice. - Then...
The columnar joints and the flower field are nearby.
(Writer)
These two?
- Given the distance... - Really?
(Columnar Joints, Goseokjeong Flower Field)
The columnar joints it is.
(Columnar Joints)
- We should go there. - I like the idea.
(They choose the columnar joints, which gives them the best shortcut.)
- Sure. - We'll stick to what's closer.
- Done. - Wait, what smells so good?
- It smells amazing. The brownie. - The brownie.
(The brownie is fully done.)
- The brownie? - Isn't that burned?
Having too little batter might've caused it to burn.
(How did the brownie made with the tong arms turn out?)
Is it done already?
I can't wait.
(He takes the brownie out.)
- What's that? - It's not cooked, right?
- Hey, it's done. - Really?
(The brownie stands as proof of their struggle.)
- No way. - Really? Let's try it then.
- Which veterans can try that? - How many years?
The 16-year veterans first, followed by the 10-year veterans?
Don't be like that and just read the room.
If you thought that,
it means you don't think you should eat it.
Act accordingly then.
- You wondered if you could join in. - Yes.
Then don't join in.
(Sad laughter)
- It came out pretty nice. - Gosh...
(They taste the brownie they made.)
There's quite a lot.
Oh, this looks lovely.
- It's... - It's good!
- Is it nice? After lunch... - This and coffee...
Hey, it's warm.
(This is what I'm talking about!)
- Is it good? - It's good.
- This is kind of like... - It would be lovely with a coffee.
(The brownie made by the chefs tastes perfect.)
It's this good?
- Gosh... - It's great.
(Lunch has arrived.)
There's quite a lot.
There's sujebi too.
(A hearty spread of acorn dishes filled with the flavors of fall)
- Oh, gosh. - Goodness.
- This is crazy. - It looks amazing.
- It's incredible. - This looks delicious.
(Savory acorn imja soup)
Thank you for the food.
(Sweet and sour tray noodles)
It looks great.
- This is crazy. - It looks so good.
Isn't this acorn jelly?
(Acorn tangsu and acorn jelly salad)
It's jelly. This is really good for you.
Gosh. The acorn jelly...
(Starting with the acorn jelly)
(Exclaiming)
What is this?
(This tastes amazing!)
- It's buckwheat. - Hey.
There's makguksu too. Look.
This is just...
(Seok Sam tries the spicy noodles.)
Hey, Se Chan. Look.
- After ten years... - Right?
(Impressed)
(Jae Seok is low on energy and tries the acorn imja soup.)
- Acorns taste great. - Right?
- Isn't this great? - It is.
(The 16-year members all have a taste.)
It tastes amazing.
(Stacking an acorn jelly tower)
- This is great. - Try this.
(Stuffing his face)
It's tasty.
(The discouraged ten-year member gets an acorn boost too.)
This is real acorn imja soup.
- This is just... - The perilla seed stuff is good.
(Exclaiming)
This is amazing.
(Kyung Hwan eats hurriedly.)
It looks so good.
- Hey. The noodles... - It's good.
(Whack)
The food is great.
(The person next to him is louder than anyone.)
It's good.
- It's crazy. - Tangsu?
My gosh.
This is such a healthy meal.
(Dipping in the tangsu sauce)
- It's the real deal. - What tangsu is it?
It's so good.
(Telling happily)
(Cheering)
- What's up with him? - Hang on.
I think I'm going deaf in this ear.
(Noise pollution)
Hey, this... It's killer.
(Loud)
In here?
(Impressed)
This 16-year veteran is too noisy.
I'm not the food fighter. He is.
(Muscle Food Fighter feels great today.)
- Look at this. - He wasn't like that, was he?
- He hated it when you did that. - Exactly.
(Overreacting)
He hated it more than anything when I reacted like that.
- Now you hate it, right? - Yes.
Here goes. I'm trying something else.
The sujebi.
Let's see the 16-year veteran eat sujebi.
What do you do?
(Exclaiming)
- The 16-year veteran. - He's eating.
The expression. The frown.
(An eating show veteran with 16 years of experience)
He frowns first. Then he eats.
(Yummy)
I can't stand it. I'm sick of it.
(My gosh!)
He makes this sound as he eats.
(It tastes good!)
Here comes the reaction!
(Satisfied roar)
Se Chan, learn from him.
What did he do? I missed it.
I'm serious, though. The food is so good.
(No one can beat the reactions of a 16-year veteran.)
- Thanks. I enjoyed it. - That was a great meal.
(After making it through the ear-piercing meal,)
Let's get in the car.
The road to the columnar joints
(they head to the columnar joints in the next slot!)
We don't have much time. It's nearing 4pm.
- Okay. - It's cooler here.
(Current time: 2:01pm)
- Focus, everyone. - I feel...
I'm here to steal the scene.
- What? - I'm a scene-stealer.
- You... - I'm at it already.
(No one is interested.)
We're back at a place we visited before.
It's actually beautiful here.
- Yes. - It's worth coming here.
(Cheorwon's famous Columnar Joint Forest Trail)
- Is it? - It's really pretty.
- Gosh. - If you walk along...
Do you know what columnar joints are?
- No. - What are they?
You don't know about them?
(A bad pun)
- Your Majesty. - Cooled lava.
- I know that phrase. - What are columnar joints?
(What are columnar joints?)
- A rock face similar to my teeth. - Yes.
(When lava cools, it hardens into jagged shapes,)
- That's right. - They're like this.
- They're crooked? - Yes.
(just like Jae Seok's teeth.)
They look like Jae Seok's teeth.
- What a grand sight. - Melted lava.
- This is amazing. - It's beautiful.
(They arrive at the columnar joints.)
It's so pretty.
This is madness.
This is just...
This is Cheorwon's Hantangang Columnar Joint Trail.
(A breathtaking view of the Hantan River Gorge,)
This is a river.
You can walk along the grand cliff and waterways...
(framed by majestic columnar joints)
and enjoy the thrilling and beautiful sights.
- It's spectacular. - It is.
There are such lovely places in Korea.
- It's really... - Oh, gosh.
(In awe)
- It's so pretty. - It's amazing.
I get to come here thanks to Running Man.
- Here... - Is all of this...
(A magnificent view)
- It's so pretty here. - columnar joints?
- They're all columnar joints. - Columnar joints.
- Isn't it beautiful? - It's beyond words.
(Columnar joints surrounding the jade-green Hantan River)
- It's so beautiful. - The water is jade-green.
It looks like a fairy could appear.
- It's lovely. Is it mission time? - It's amazing.
- Yes. - I'll take a photo for you.
You still haven't understood the rules yet?
We must pass all the missions.
- Yes. - I just asked to confirm.
I asked. Here's another columnar joint.
(Getting revenge)
- I found one. - Let's do this.
(Mini Cheorwon)
It's lovely here.
- Before doing the actual mission, - Yes.
let's see who gets the penalty for this slot.
- Oh, dear. - It's time I showed up.
- It's Jae Seok. - The rocks are like his teeth.
(The columnar joints are like his teeth.)
- Yes. Jae Seok's teeth. - Exactly.
(Is Jae Seok's photo in the slot?)
I think it's Jae Seok.
- It's Jae Seok. - Here goes. 1, 2...
- Right? - Is it me?
(Columnar joints)
- It's Jae Seok. - You were right.
(The teeth prediction was correct.)
- No wonder. - No wonder.
Is it him because this place looks like his teeth?
(Was it Chan Hee's deliberate choice?)
- It looks like it. - Then...
Jae Seok's face was there, so you'll get a penalty.
(Current penalty candidates)
It's three out of four.
(Kyung Hwan, Seok Jin, Jae Seok, and Ye Eun)
I need us to fail this time.
- What? No. - Come on.
This mission is called Full Sentence Charades.
- How does it work? - On top of a bridge...
with a hole in the center where you get a 360-degree view,
- What? - What?
five of you will play charades.
You must get at least 3 out of 5 correct.
- There's a hole? - We're good at this.
- That must be it. - It's that place.
We're good at this.
Over there?
- Gosh. It's pretty, but... - Yes.
(The suspension bridge here)
- I'm too scared. - I'm scared.
I can't... Why must we do that here?
(This is a nightmare for the scaredy-cats.)
I think the bridge moves.
(They'll be battling in midair with open space all around them.)
I'm yawning. This is a bad sign.
I can't look down.
I suddenly need the toilet.
- Me too. I need to poop. - Right?
You get 100 seconds per question.
We can do this.
Four of you must describe the question,
and each of you will get a different part of the sentence.
(A worm dances to attract butterflies.)
You must copy the previous gestures...
(A worm dances.)
and then add your own to complete the sentence.
- That's the basic rule. - That's tough.
(A worm dances to attract butterflies.)
The person guessing must say the full sentence.
- This game... - It's not easy.
You need a good memory.
Isn't this a "Family Game Show" thing?
- Yes. - It's like that.
- Yes. - It's not "Family Game Show."
(What's with that tone?)
If we fail this mission, is it a complete failure?
(Current time: 2:20pm)
- Within the time limit... - We have until 4pm.
If you don't complete a line before 4pm, you fail.
(Did he nod?)
There's no time. It's already past two.
Jae Seok, you sound like you don't plan to succeed.
(Jae Seok is already scared.)
- We must. - Let's do this.
- Let's have a go. - We can do this.
- We do this or make another line. - Yes.
- It's been 16 years. - Yes. It's been 16 years.
(Team Running Man claims they can communicate with just a look.)
- We're amazing at charades. - Hey.
Other than Se Chan and Ye Eun, we've been here for 16 years.
Yes.
That's a fully accurate sentence.
(Old Fossil Jee is unusually sharp with his calculations today.)
Can you separate the 10- and 2-year members too?
- Two-year you can't even imagine. - Se Chan. I know.
(Whispering)
You need at least ten years' experience to brag.
Not even you have bragging rights, though.
(Scoffing)
Me? I'll make that Old Keu Keu pay.
- Oh, gosh. - It's a lovely walkway.
(They make their way to the mission spot.)
This is so nice.
I'm scared of what's beneath us.
- So am I. - What's this?
(They step onto a bridge with a see-through floor.)
- Don't look down. - When I was here last time...
Gosh. This is incredible.
This spot is a bit scary.
- It's scary. - This is bad.
(You can see everything.)
- It's getting scarier. - I can't hold up my camera.
(Hoarse groans of fear)
I'm scared.
Would I die if I fell from here?
(The imaginative type)
- I can't look down, Seok Jin. - I just had a dizzy spell.
(The scaredy-cats are shaking.)
Gosh. What a killer view.
(But there's a man calmly enjoying the view.)
This is great.
This is nice. Look at the water.
(An Anyang native speaking in a Gyeongsang accent...)
(while admiring the scenery of Gangwon Province)
- This is amazing. - I can't go on.
- I can't go further. - Oh, no.
It's pretty over here.
It's pretty.
(Agreeing)
It's just amazing.
Hurry up. What are you doing in the back, Haha?
(Meanwhile, the scaredy-cats are falling behind.)
(Moaning in fear)
- Haha. - What now? I'm feeling it.
The ten-year member will help you.
What do I do? I can't...
(The original scaredy-cat froze up.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Why are you walking like that?
(Why are you walking so slowly like that?)
It's the bridge. He's scared.
- I see. - Oh, no. Hey...
(Okay)
- Beneath us... - Oh, no. Hey, hey...
(Dragging Haha)
- Hello. Is it scary? - I can't walk.
(They arrive at a fork.)
Oh, no. What do I do?
Where do we play the game?
We marked the spot with an X.
- Okay. - Go to each spot one by one.
X marks the spot.
(Current location, mission spot)
We're practically in the air.
(This isolated bridge...)
That wire holds the bridge up.
(is today's mission spot.)
Gosh. Hang on.
(Serious)
- We all have to go? - Yes. We start when you're ready.
Those who aren't scared can take the furthest spots.
I'll go, then.
(He's trying to make the younger ones do it.)
- Goodness. - You know...
- I see you and think... - It's just...
(Making a promise to himself)
I shouldn't become like you when I'm older.
- No. I'm being honest. - You teach me a lot.
- I can't go that far. - Ji Hyo!
(Sweet)
- I'm too scared. - Ji Hyo!
- Yes? - You're not scared, are you?
Go over there.
(He gives the order in the sweetest way possible.)
- Ji Hyo. Go over there. - No one can go over there.
Let's get moving. Be quick.
(The fearless Kook enters the bridge first.)
Oh, I see them. The X marks.
Get over here quick!
- Shoot. - I'm scared.
- I'm too scared. - I'm too scared.
(The scaredy-cats can't move.)
I'm too scared.
This is just amazing.
It's nice.
(Chuckling happily)
(He's passing the time by filming a vlog.)
The water moving... Hurry up!
We're practically in the air.
(Ji Hyo, Kyung Hwan)
(The less frightened ones also step onto the bridge.)
Look straight ahead and walk!
- It's just as bad. - We must hurry.
(The scaredy-cats start moving now.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do this quickly.
- Let's just go. - Be quick.
- Oh, gosh. - Nevis!
(They say these words whenever they have a chance.)
- The Nevis Swing! - This is hardcore.
(Dizzy)
- This is hardcore. - I hate this.
(Moaning in fear)
- I'm so scared. - Ye Eun.
I don't want to do this.
- I really want to end this quickly. - I swear.
(They're basically crawling.)
Me too.
- Stand on the X. - Ye Eun. Take your place.
Look far ahead.
(Holding tightly)
I really... Why are we doing this?
- Let's be quick. - Hurry up!
- Holding the bar won't save you! - True.
(Frustrated)
- This is really... - Come on...
(Everyone entered the game.)
- Don't. - Seriously.
- Why are we doing this? - Which way do I face?
The first four people...
- will do the gestures. - Okay.
The fifth person must guess the sentence.
We'll start from this end.
(Guesser)
- Okay. - Okay. Make it quick.
- Be quick. - Hold on tight!
- We'll be quick. - Give us the question!
(Rushing)
- Don't run! - Don't run!
(Going back and forth)
Haha's struggling!
(Tip)
- I keep farting. - Okay.
Haha keeps farting.
(Breaking news)
I want to pee.
(Of all people, the four scaredy-cats have to explain.)
- I'm losing my mind. - The bridge is swaying.
You must do the previous motion and then add your own part.
(Nervous)
- Hurry up. - If you have a good memory,
(Everyone gets a keyword.)
- you should go later. - Shall we begin?
- Why are we doing this here? - Let's begin.
(Round 1 starts.)
- Jae Seok. - Okay.
- Go ahead. - Hurry up and go.
(Ye Eun's keyword: A frilled lizard)
What?
(A frilled lizard)
What's that? An item?
(Glancing)
- Gosh, I'm scared. - What?
(Crying)
Hurry up.
(A frilled lizard)
(All right.)
(She manages to finish explaining her part.)
(A frilled lizard and a water strider)
Why are we doing this here?
(Checking his keyword)
(At this place)
I can't look down.
(Flat)
Hey, don't move.
(A cruel mission to imitate this animal)
I'm good as long as the bridge doesn't shake.
(A frilled lizard and a water strider)
Are you guys doing this?
- Hurry up. - All right.
(He portrays a frilled lizard first.)
- You know what it is, right? - Yes, I do.
- And... - Okay.
It moves like...
(Screaming)
I can't look down.
(Describing a water strider)
What's that?
- Surfing. - No.
(Whispering)
It's surfing.
- Okay. This is it, right? - No.
All right.
I want to leave.
(The scaredy-cat quickly brushed through the explanation.)
I don't know what it is. All right.
(It's time to relay the keywords to Haha.)
- This... - Okay.
This...
What?
(Pretending to surf)
- Did you read the keyword? - Yes.
What's that?
- Why is the bridge moving? - This and...
And...
(A frilled lizard and a water strider...)
(did synchronized swimming.)
(Got it.)
- Okay. - It's a sentence.
- Hey, Se Chan. - Yes.
(It's time to describe it to Se Chan, the guesser.)
This is Ye Eun's part.
- A lizard. - Then comes...
Jae Seok's part.
Like this?
(Okay)
And this is Seok Jin's part.
Okay.
Synchronized swimming.
- And this is my part. - Okay.
(And ate watermelon.)
Watermelon.
(Correct)
Synchronized swimming and watermelon.
Se Chan, say the answer.
(It's time to answer.)
- A frilled lizard... - That's right.
A frilled lizard...
(Did he figure out the water strider?)
What's this?
Turn them into a sentence.
A frilled lizard...
walked on...
It walked on a single-log bridge,
did synchronized swimming,
- and ate a watermelon. - Is it correct?
- Incorrect. - Why?
(It was close, but he got it wrong.)
- What? - Which part was wrong?
- What? - A frilled lizard...
- Mine was "And ate watermelon." - And a water strider.
(Not a single-log bridge)
Was it a water strider?
(But he got 3 right out of 4.)
How was I supposed to describe a water strider?
- I was so close. - A water strider is a hard one.
You should've gotten down to the floor.
- Hey, we lost. - We lost.
- We lost. - I really can't do this.
(He's already looking crushed after describing just one question.)
The bridge shook just now.
- What should I do? - Do you need to use the restroom?
I finished farting. I want to poop now.
Haha might poop. Be careful.
(He's about to fart.)
(Blocking his hole)
- I see. An alpaca. - An alpaca was a hard one.
(They fail Round 2.)
An alpaca kissed.
- Let's do better. - I'll do better.
Why don't we change up the order?
(They have to get all 3 questions right to complete the mission.)
Let's change up the order.
- Jong Kook, go second. - Here I come.
- Oh, my goodness. - Move.
(Flabbergasted)
- Let's hurry up. - Move!
(They're already terrified, and he walks past aggressively.)
- Hey. - Move!
- Stop it. - Move, okay?
- Jong Kook. - I can't believe him.
(The lineup has changed.)
- What should I do with this? - Going first is the best.
Haha, will you guess the answer?
(If they get it wrong this time, they'll fail the mission!)
- Let's go. Let's do this. - This is driving me crazy.
- Let's go. - We need to do this.
Okay. Here I go.
(Round 3 begins.)
- Here I go. - Okay.
(An anteater)
- You need to figure it out. - Okay.
(Poking)
(Licking the ants)
It isn't an elephant.
It looks like this.
- An archerfish? - No.
So it does this.
(Licking)
- It does this. Okay. - All right.
- All right. You got it. - Hey.
- You got it. - Yes. Here.
- Here. - Go slow.
(Anteater)
(It's time to explain the next part.)
For goodness' sake.
A forward roll.
(An anteater did a forward roll.)
(Detective Kim figures it out by watching him wriggle.)
What?
- I'm exhausted. - Okay.
- Is that it? - That's it.
(Amazed)
- Two? - I did two.
- Ji Hyo, it's easy. - Good.
(An anteater did a forward roll.)
- It's easy. - Okay.
(Anteater)
Okay.
He'll actually do it.
(He describes a forward roll without any fear.)
And...
(Explaining the next part)
(Saw "blank")
Okay.
We'll succeed in it this time.
- This is driving me crazy. - Good.
(She describes it to Jae Seok, the guesser!)
- Watch carefully. - Okay.
Why are we doing this here?
(Asking the fundamental question)
Ji Hyo is an actor.
(Licking the ants)
- Why... Hey. - That's it.
- Hey. - That's it.
An anteater rolled...
(Rolling forward)
Okay.
(Explaining the next part)
(Explaining the last part)
Let's turn them into a sentence.
An anteater did a forward roll,
saw an orangutan, and fell in love.
It's correct.
(If they get this one wrong, they'll fail the mission!)
We're amazing...
- at Speak With Your Actions. - We go back 16 years.
(Did he answer correctly?)
- Correct. - Okay.
(Correct)
- Jae Seok. - We did it.
(High five, taking it back)
- Well done. - All right.
- Okay. - Get two more questions right...
- to succeed in the mission. - Two more questions.
Two more questions.
- Two more questions? - Two more questions? Oh, my gosh.
- Two more questions? - Oh, my gosh.
(Struggling)
- Let's go this way. - I like the order.
- From there to here? - Okay.
- Go. - Am I guessing the answer?
(A constipated zombie and a sloth did a headspin.)
- Hurry up. - Okay. I can do it.
Set.
(Round 4 begins.)
(A constipated zombie and a sloth did a headspin.)
(Explaining)
Okay.
(Haha is explaining it to Jae Seok.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
(Constipated)
My stomach hurts. Why isn't it coming out?
(Acting out a zombie)
Okay.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Jae Seok.
(Constipation)
(Zombie)
(Sloth)
(Glancing over)
(Dazed)
(She doesn't have a clue.)
Moving slowly?
(She has no idea.)
Going forward? So...
(Sloth!)
What?
(Chuckling)
(Zoned-out Ji Hyo finally figures it out.)
- Watch. - I think she figured it out.
(Not much time remains.)
Pooping.
- Constipation. - Yes.
(A constipated...)
Zombie.
(zombie...)
A zombie is constipated.
Cicada? What's that?
Sloth.
(and a sloth...)
A constipated zombie and a sloth...
(He got 3 right in an instant.)
- Now comes my part. - Okay.
(If he gets this part, they'll succeed!)
- All right. - Okay.
(A headspin is a difficult keyword.)
It's so hard.
A headspin.
(A constipated zombie and a sloth did a headspin.)
Okay.
A constipated zombie...
and a sloth did a headspin.
- Correct. - No way.
(He guesses the answer correctly!)
No way.
He answered correctly.
(The quick-witted Detective Kim gave the perfect answer.)
Am I right?
- That's incredible. - You're right.
- The last one. - Only one question remains.
We're nearly there.
Are we changing the order?
(Get the final question right, and they complete the mission!)
- One, two, three, four. - What?
- Will Ji Hyo guess the answer? - Am I going fourth?
(Final Round, Guesser: Ji Hyo)
Will Ji Hyo be able to answer correctly?
She can do it.
She has done it before.
Don't worry, Ji Hyo. Guess the answer.
- Set. - Will she know what it is?
(The final round begins.)
Go.
(Showing her crooked teeth)
Let's do this.
Teeth.
- Yu Jae Seok? - No.
- Teeth. - Teeth.
- Crooked teeth. - Teeth.
Okay.
Ready?
Teeth. I see.
- Yu Jae Seok. - No.
(Confusing the members unintentionally)
- Columnar joints. - It's as it is.
- Someone with twisted teeth. - Yes.
(Okay)
(Explaining the second part)
(A mermaid)
(Shocked)
(Flapping)
(He gets a cruel keyword again.)
You need to lie down.
(About to cry)
(He has to explain this part now.)
For goodness' sake! Why did you...
(Getting down slowly)
Tadpole?
(No)
Worm?
Seok Jin, make a pretty facial expression.
(Whispering)
Maggot?
(Adding sexiness)
I see. Mermaid.
You can't talk to each other.
Why are you so bad at it?
(It's time for bungee jumping.)
(Showing her crooked teeth, a mermaid bungee jumped.)
Stop.
(They're struggling because the bridge is shaking so much.)
I'm scared.
(A proper diving position)
(Proud)
I can't believe I did it.
- It's easy. - Okay.
(They finally get to Ji Hyo.)
Teeth. Twisted.
Crooked teeth.
(Showing her crooked teeth)
Misaligned teeth.
That looks so dirty.
- I'm exhausted. - Look at him.
Trainer.
Jong Kook looks ridiculous.
Mermaid.
(A mermaid)
A mermaid with crooked teeth.
(Bungee jumped)
Bungee jumping.
(It's time for the last part!)
Not much time remains!
(They have 15 seconds left.)
- Oh, my. We're nearly there. - Okay.
- We're almost done. - We're nearly there.
Swimming.
We're nearly there.
(Piranha)
- A mermaid without front teeth. - Ji Hyo, concentrate...
- a bit more. - What's this?
- Here and there. - What's this?
- Swimming. - No!
- We're in trouble. - Ji Hyo.
(Can Ji Hyo figure out that it's a piranha?)
- Just get it wrong. - Five,
four, three, two, one.
The fish that bites people.
What's the answer?
(Time's up.)
The fish that bites people.
(She has to answer now!)
- Think about it. - Showing her crooked teeth,
a mermaid bungee jumped...
I don't think she knows the answer.
It's okay to get it wrong, Ji Hyo.
(Will Ji Hyo say piranha?)
- Ji Hyo, just go. - Shout it out.
Met a piranha in the water.
Correct!
(Perfect answer)
- It's over. - Really?
(The last-second buzzer-beater pays off big.)
- We did it. - That was incredible.
- No way. - Ji Hyo, it has been 16 years.
- It has been 16 years. - Go that way.
- With three correct answers, - All set.
you got the bingo slot.
(They manage to pull off a bingo on the Columnar Joints row.)
- Let's go. Go straight. - Hurry up.
- Let's go. - Come on.
(Running away)
- I feel queasy. - Come on.
- You did well. - Piranha.
(Current time, 2:48pm)
- Piranha. - Well done.
Kyung Hwan,
(They found a snack bar.)
- do you want something? - Something cold.
- Please buy us a multigrain shake. - Hey.
- Hi. Three times six is eighteen. - Who is paying?
(While Jae Seok is trying to pay)
- Jae Seok is. - Not me.
Three times six is eighteen.
(Touching)
So...
(The oldest member has no intention to pay.)
Multigrain shake.
(The multigrain shake looks thick even at a glance.)
- Thank you. - She made it thick.
- Multigrain shake. - She made it thick.
It isn't sweet.
(He loves it.)
- Multigrain shake? - Yes.
- Oh, my. - It's tasty, right?
(The taste that makes the motion sickness disappear instantly)
- Go ahead. - Very nice.
Jae Seok, we need to go here next.
(The next bingo place)
- The flower field. - Jae Seok.
Goseokjeong Flower Field.
- I'm a flower pot. - A flower pot.
(Goseokjeong Flower Field)
I bet the Flower Field has my mission.
(If they secure this square, they'll make a bingo.)
I have that hunch.
- Thank you for the drink. - Who paid for it?
(What mission awaits the members at Goseokjeong Flower Field?)
- Mr. Yu did. - Thank you for the drink.
I feel queasy.
(Seok Sam is carsick because of the columnar joints.)
- Do you know how it feels? - I feel dizzy.
- Well... - I don't want to hear it!
I'm sorry, but I think there are two kids.
There are multiple kids.
- There are two. - Yes.
It's like a fight between grandpas.
"What do you know?"
(Grandpa 1)
(Grandpa 2)
"I'm better than you!"
But they can't live without each other.
- They always call and meet up. - "Stop it!"
- Since it was funny... - They fight all the time.
They fight all the time.
(The grandpa duo will bicker until their last day on earth.)
Since it was funny, I'll let you off this once.
I really want to talk.
I really want to share how I'm feeling right now.
(Laughing)
- "I don't want to hear it." - I don't want to hear it.
(The place they arrived at after failing to say it out loud)
What's this place?
- It's pretty. - Goseokjeong Flower Field.
- It's such a nice place. - I know.
(Goseokjeong Flower Field with fall flowers in bloom)
- This place is so pretty. - Now,
- the penalty... - Flowers make Jong Kook go crazy.
They make me go crazy. I love flowers.
(Filled with flowers that Jong Kook loves)
- This place is for Jong Kook. - I love pink flowers.
(Goseokjeong Flower Field)
This is Cheorwon's representative tourist attraction,
Goseokjeong Flower Field.
Before we begin the mission,
let's see who will receive the penalty if you fail...
(Who is the penalty candidate for Goseokjeong Flower Field square?)
- the mission here. - Who is it?
- Please remove the sticker. - I'm so curious.
- Shall I remove it? - Yes.
Jong Kook is related to flowers.
I think it'll be me.
In 1, 2, 3.
- It's Joker. - Joker?
- Good. - This is the Joker Slot.
(Here's the Joker square.)
Since it doesn't have anyone's face,
you need to pick one person who will take the penalty.
But this is...
(What's the mission that'll decide the penalty taker?)
The Joker mission is...
Pick Up First to Survive.
It'll be a 4-on-4 team competition.
Two players will enter from each team...
and tie their feet together like it's a three-legged race.
Then they'll run toward the sponge stick on the other side,
grab it 1st, and hit a member of the other team for 1 point.
This is bad.
The team that gets more points will win.
(The team with a higher score after 3 rounds wins.)
One member of the losing team will take the penalty.
We divided the members into two teams.
The members whose faces have been revealed,
(Team Yellow: Kyung Hwan, Seok Jin, Jae Seok, Ye Eun)
Kyung Hwan, Seok Jin,
Jae Seok, and Ye Eun will be a team.
- Gosh. - We're a team.
(Team Green: Jong Kook, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, Haha)
Jong Kook, Se Chan,
- Ji Hyo, and Haha will be a team. - Gosh.
(The 4 on Team Yellow are already penalty candidates.)
If we win, someone from that team will take the penalty.
(They must win to lower the chance of getting the penalty.)
I'll show the strength of the member with ten years of experience.
- Give me a break. - We'll win no matter what.
- We have confidence. - Give me a break.
(The eldest ones set out for Team Yellow.)
- Shall I take this side? - Come to this side.
I'll do that.
Why did you enter the game?
I had to compete against you.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan set out for Team Green.)
- Why did you enter the game? - I'll end you!
- I'll teach you a lesson. - Gosh, my physique...
Are we tying our feet together as well?
(The 4 of them are tied together.)
- Why... - Our feet too?
- Jong Kook and... - This won't work.
(Anxious)
I can pull out his hair, right?
(A fierce scuffle is expected.)
Let's go.
- Let's have fun - We can win.
(Relaxed)
- What should I do? - This game makes no sense.
(Kim Muscles is already excited at the thought of playing with them.)
- Let's have fun - Heave-ho.
(Squeezing his side)
- Let's go. - Let's have
(Hitting)
- Fun - It hurts!
(The two eldest are no match physically.)
- Let's have fun - It hurts!
You just need to be swift.
Exactly.
- You never know. - Good luck, my teammates.
(The key is to grab the sponge stick first.)
Good luck.
- Seok Sam. - Get ready.
(Round 1 begins.)
Okay. Don't do that with your shoulder.
- Okay. - Set.
- Let's go. - If he does that...
(Grabbing both his arms)
Okay. Let's go.
(Humming)
- Arms around the shoulders - We need to grab it first.
(Jong Kook grabs Jae Seok with one hand and shakes him up.)
- Arms around the shoulders - Hey.
- Arms around the shoulders - Hey, Seok Sam.
(Flailing)
- It tickles. - Arms around the shoulders
(He tickles Seok Jin with the other hand.)
- Shoulders - Stop it.
Arms around the shoulders
(Giggling)
- Arms around the shoulders - Come on.
(They move forward together.)
- Hey. Hold on. - Arms around the shoulders
- Are you playing with us? - Arms around the shoulders
You punk!
(Annoyed, Jee-rasoni makes a weak attack.)
- Your forehead is shiny. - Arms
(Not affected)
- Seok Jin. - This won't do.
(Pitiful)
- Get it together. - People think we'll lose, right?
- Get it together. Okay. - But we can win.
(Determined)
(The two members renew their resolution.)
- We can win. - Okay. Get it together.
Jae Seok, let's win.
- Arms around the shoulders - Arms around the shoulders
(The man who is crazy about putting his arms around the shoulders...)
(doesn't give them a break.)
- Arms around the shoulders - Eusshara eussha!
(The two older members flail.)
Eusshara eussha!
(The weakest member pretends to enjoy himself.)
Seok Jin, get it together.
(Father...)
Oh, no.
- I feel bad for him. - Oh, no.
Is putting one foot forward your strategy?
- I wouldn't say that, but... - Is it your strategy?
(Swinging)
It won't work.
- Why do I smell grilled fish? - Is it your strategy?
(His sense of smell broke after being harassed.)
- Grilled fish... - Is it your strategy?
(Jae Seok is being adored in the meantime.)
- Is this right? - Seok Sam.
- We came this far. - We don't have a strategy.
(Thinking)
- Okay. - If we jump...
(At the same time)
- Right. - Will you jump?
(Sharing their strategy while the others are listening)
- Yes. In 2, 3. - In 2, 3.
(Flapping)
(Jong Kook's legs don't even budge.)
(Shouting)
(The toothpick ends up teleporting.)
Seriously.
(Come on!)
Seriously. This is...
This hurts my pride.
- You have to win. - You can do it.
Old soldiers still have it.
You guys should lose.
- It's time for a strategy. - Lie down.
(Turning)
It's time for a strategy.
(Grabbing)
- Ssaebssaeb. - Lie down.
(Panting)
- Ssaebssaeb. - Grab him.
Seok Jin, grab him. Grab Se Chan.
(Jee-rasoni attacks when Se Chan's guard is down.)
(It's the pushover he's already beaten before.)
We need to grab Ssaebssaeb.
- Throw him down. - We need to grab Ssaebssaeb.
Do you think it'll work?
(Gritting his teeth)
- Really? - Yes, I think it'll work.
- Do you think you have a chance? - Seok Jin.
(Laughing)
- How does it feel? - Jae Seok, help him.
(Grabbing tight)
- How does it feel? - Jae Seok.
(The two can't do anything as Jong Kook is holding them.)
- How does it feel? - Grab him.
- Jae Seok, go. - Tell me.
Tell me how it feels.
(Jong Kook's toy is moving as he controls.)
How does it feel?
(Forced blues dancing)
- Tell me. - My goodness.
- I'm so annoyed. - How does it feel?
Don't pick on my teammates!
- Just finish it, Se Chan. - Finish it.
- Just hurry up and do it. - Hold on.
(Se Chan grabbed the stick.)
Finish it.
Let go of my arms.
Grab it. You can do it.
You're nearly there.
Why can't you do it? It's here. Go.
(The 10 Years pay back for the suffering they went through.)
It's here. Go.
What's your strategy now?
(Crying)
- What's your strategy now? - You punk!
(Feeling angry, Jee-rasoni fights back meekly.)
- You didn't hit me yet. - I didn't hit you yet.
- Where do I need to hit? - The head.
- The head? - Call the police.
- Where do I need to hit? - Call the police.
(Hitting excitedly)
- Call the police. - Shall I hit the head?
Hey, you're too much.
I hit the head.
(Team Green wins Round 1.)
Hey.
- This is fun. - You hit my hat.
- Oh, no. - It's a marionette.
Your hat?
(Team Yellow gets beaten mercilessly.)
- Team Jong Kook won. - For goodness' sake.
- Seriously. - I'm so annoyed.
How can we beat them?
(Team Green 1, Team Yellow 0)
You're our only hope.
- So what happens... - We need a tie.
- if I win? - Hey.
(Kyung Hwan is Team Yellow's only hope.)
- Then we'll have a final match. - You need to win...
- no matter what. - You're our only hope, Kyung Hwan.
Heo Kyung Hwan!
Ye Eun, let's do this seriously.
- We can be funny afterward. - Okay.
(Serious)
- I won't try to be funny. - Let's do this seriously.
(The bride-to-be has determination on another level.)
- They tormented our teammates. - I know.
(For the members who were harrassed)
- You can do it. - All right.
(Jiu-jitsu Heo's revenge time)
We can do it. We got this.
- Ddochi... - Get ready. Set.
(Round 2 begins.)
Let's be friendly...
- at first. - Let's do that.
- Let's be friendly. - Fighting here will be meaningless.
(They'll move together at first.)
Set, go.
- Let's be friendly. Left foot. - Right foot, left foot.
- Right foot, left foot. - Okay.
- Let's be friendly. - Let's be friendly.
(Staggering)
- Right now... - Go slow.
Okay. It's over.
- Ye Eun, get up. - I mean...
(The paper doll fell after a few steps.)
- Let's be friendly. - Ye Eun, get up.
Get up. You need to walk.
- Go slow. - Left foot.
(Going forward, ignoring her)
- Right foot. - Go slow.
(Getting dragged)
- Left foot. - Ye Eun, don't let him drag you.
- Right foot. - Ye Eun, don't let him drag you.
(The bride-to-be is battered.)
- Right foot. - She is trying to be funny.
- Be careful. - Why are you so strong?
(Gosh)
- Heave-ho. - All right.
(Kyung Hwan gets down.)
All right. Let's go.
(Grabbing)
The jiu-jitsu athlete lay down.
- The jiu-jitsu athlete lay down. - Come on.
We need to win.
(Jiu-jitsu Heo flipped the two at once.)
There you go. Jiu-jitsu.
Let's go.
(He uses a jiu-jitsu technique.)
My groin!
(Thighs fully open)
His groin.
- Be careful. - Bite him.
- Mind the middle part. - Hold on.
(The paper doll crawls toward the sponge stick.)
No. Get there first.
- Ye Eun is going. - Grab it.
(Grabbing)
- Ye Eun, grab it. - We're all tangled up!
Ji Hyo, you need to get up.
(Strong Ji Hyo grabbed Ye Eun so she can't go.)
- We're all tangled up! - Don't do jiu-jitsu.
- Hey. - Hurry up.
(The gibbon stretches out her arm.)
- Ji Hyo, no. - Ye Eun, grab it.
(She almost reached it.)
My foot...
Ye Eun can reach it.
(Will Team Yellow win?)
Ye Eun, grab it.
Ye Eun, hurry up. Ye Eun, grab it.
(Moving)
- My underwear will show! - Ye Eun!
- My underwear will show, Ji Hyo! - Ye Eun!
Ji Hyo, my underwear will show! I'm serious.
(Turning serious)
My underwear will show! My underwear!
(The bride-to-be explodes as her underwear might show.)
- We won! - My underwear will show!
- Nice. - We won.
(Team Yellow wins Round 2 with Ye Eun securing her underwear.)
- I'm tired. - We did it.
- It's 1 to 1, and Team Yellow wins. - It's 1 to 1.
- Final round! - Pick the best members,
(The ace members of both teams will participate in the finals.)
and we'll have the last match.
Why don't we do it separately?
(Each team)
- We can do it in pairs. - Going fast in separate places.
(Suggesting a pair race to keep the game tense.)
- Let's do a race. - We can run quickly.
- We can still fight. - Okay.
- Then Ye Eun... - Come, Seok Jin.
- Okay, then Ye Eun... - Yes. Seok Sam.
- No! - Why?
I don't want to play with Seok Jin.
Do it with Kyung Hwan.
- Do it with Kyung Hwan. - Do it with Kyung Hwan.
It's about speed.
(The daughter rejects sharply.)
- It's about speed. I'm slow. - Hey.
We'll win.
You know...
- I'm a bit hurt. - Seriously.
(Now that I think about it...)
- Hey. - She hated it.
- She hated it. - When we were singing...
- We have to win. - "Milkshake" and all.
(Don't misunderstand me.)
- We have to win. - We even sang together.
(The Jee-Ji clan breaks up for the victory.)
- We have to win. - You're right.
You're right.
Turn.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo set out for Team Green.)
- Let's practice. - Okay. Where are you?
(As they've been on the show for 26 years,)
We can go quicker.
(they have perfect teamwork.)
- Let's go. - Ready, go. One, two.
(Ye Eun and Kyung Hwan also practice.)
- One, two. - One, two.
- One, two. - Turn!
(The short-legs and Eight-Foot Tall Ghost...)
- Good job. - I'm going faster than normal.
(have great teamwork considering it's their first time.)
- Good job, Ye Eun. - They're fast.
They're really slow.
- They're fast. - They're fast.
(Dashing)
They're really fast.
- They're fast. - They're fast.
(The siblings are super fast.)
Stop now. Don't show them.
- Don't show them. - They're fast.
(Anxious)
Nice!
(Last round to decide who will take the penalty)
You have to grab the stick and hit the other team to win.
Go to that side. Go over there.
- Go over there. - Go further.
(A tense battle of nerves)
- Okay. - But...
- They're at an advantage. - Why?
You'll grab with your right. They have to grab with their left.
- They can use their right hand. - They can use their right hand.
(What are you talking about?)
- Okay. - Think it through.
- What are you talking about? - I have my right hand.
- It's okay. - Okay.
Ready, go!
(The final round begins.)
Go. One, two.
- Nice. - One, two.
Go.
- One, two. - Nice.
(Both teams are running at the same pace.)
One, two.
(By the way, they're trying to run.)
It's over.
(Laughing)
Hurry up!
(The tall one and the little one fell pitifully.)
- Get up quickly! - They won't be able to catch up.
(The Mighty Siblings grabbed the stick first.)
- This is 16 years plus 10 years. - It's 16 years.
(The years they spent on Running Man)
- That's right. - Sixteen years.
(If they hit their opponent with the sponge stick, they win.)
- That's too harsh. - You hit them.
- It's hot. - You hit them.
(Whoosh)
Look at him.
(Jiu-jitsu Heo tries to avoid the stick until the very end.)
You always keep asking to get hit by acting like that.
- Come here. - You're asking to get hit.
(He clenches his teeth with determination.)
Come here.
(He even took off his shoe.)
Watch your back.
(Hitting)
Watch your back. Turn off the camera!
(Jiu-jitsu Heo and Mr. Yang's beating show)
- Jiu-jitsu... - They're our comedians.
They're our comedians.
That was funny.
(The performance ends successfully.)
- That was funny! - Our comedians!
(Team Green wins with a score of 2 to 1.)
- Team Green wins. - That was nice.
You completed a line of the Rip and Crush Cheorwon Bingo.
(Completing a bingo by winning the Joker square)
- Yes. - Okay!
(Current time: 3:52pm)
(They completed the mission within the given time.)
The final penalty receivers...
are Heo Kyung Hwan, Jee Seok Jin, Yu Jae Seok,
(With Team Green's win, the penalty taker will be decided...)
(among the 4 members.)
and Ji Ye Eun, whose faces are on the board.
One person will be exempt, right?
Yes. We said there will be three penalty receivers.
We have draw tickets here.
(They'll pick 3 penalty takers by drawing lots.)
If you pick a ticket with a circle, you'll be getting the penalty.
- A circle means you're getting it. - Is that right?
Seok Sam escapes the penalty these days.
- Take any of them. - I'll take this.
(They randomly pick the tickets.)
If there's an X, you're exempt. Kyung Hwan.
(Kyung Hwan opens first.)
- Circle means penalty. - A circle, please.
(O: Penalty, X: Exempted from penalty)
One, two,
- Circle. - three!
- Okay. - Kyung Hwan is confirmed.
Confirmed.
Okay.
- Ji Ye Eun. One, two, three. - Confirmed.
A circle. Yes. It's one of us.
(Ye Eun is getting the penalty.)
(One of them will be exempt from the penalty.)
(Seok Sam hasn't gotten the penalty for 6 times in a row.)
One, two, three!
(Will he be able to avoid it today as well?)
(Jae Seok versus Seok Jin)
(Who will take the penalty?)
- Goodness. - No way.
(Seok Jin is exempt from receiving the penalty.)
Yes!
- Goodness. - No way.
We have to stop him.
(The old fox is on a roll.)
Seok Sam...
- He's on a roll. - That's unbelievable.
- We have to stop him. - He really is on a roll.
He was the strongest candidate.
I don't receive penalties these days.
(Feeling smug)
Okay!
Today's penalty is to ride this train...
- Okay. - around Goseokjeong Flower Field...
and film a promotional video.
- Goodness. - That's nice.
It's nice.
This is nice.
(Jae Seok, Kyung Hwan, and Ye Eun get on the train.)
- I wanted to get on the train. - Okay.
- Let's go. - It's refreshing.
(The other members get on as well to see the flowers.)
- It's refreshing. - This is nice!
This is so nice.
(Come here, drone!)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - It's beautiful.
(Goseokjeong Flower Field is bathed in various colors.)
- Thank you! - It's so beautiful.
- Goodness. - Okay.
(Saying hello to passersby)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Jae Seok!
- Hello. - Hello.
(Jae Seok is super popular in Cheorwon as well.)
Hello.
Jae Seok is so well-known.
- Yes. He's practically a president. - He's like a president.
Hello. I'm a man of Gangwon Province.
Hello. My hometown is Jeongseon.
(Jee Seok Sam, born in Jeongseon, Gangwon Province)
- Seok Sam's hometown is Jeongseon, - Yes.
but when he comes to Gangwon Province,
- Right. - no one recognizes him.
(Even in Gangwon Province)
- No one... - It's not far from here.
(The star Jeongseon gave but forgot)
- He's not known by the people here. - They have no idea.
- So we each have to say something. - Right.
(Penalty: Saying a promotional comment to promote the field)
This flower field is like our lives.
May it always be this beautiful.
It's breathtaking and incredible.
- Kyung Hwan. - Heo Kyung Hwan.
Do you want to know where we are? Give me Cheorwon. I'll tell you.
Cheorwon.
(Satisfied with his witty remark)
- Cheorwon. - That was good.
- These pink muhly... - They're pretty.
They're pretty, they're pretty
(Jong Sook is excited to see the flowers.)
Jong Kook is crazy about the flowers.
They're really... How pretty.
- Jong Kook is really... - Goodness.
(Saving it with his eyes and a video)
- He's admiring the flowers. - Jong Kook...
(Cheorwon's fall colored the heart of Jong Sook.)
Goodness.
- They... - It really is a flower field.
Just looking at them is so relaxing.
Come on.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Hey! - Hey!
- Bye! - Run
- The sun is setting. - Here comes the rice.
(It's finally time for dinner.)
- Goodness. - Too bad.
- Goodness. - It's burnt!
(With the unhinged cooking villains in action,)
(dinner is becoming increasingly uncertain.)
- Be quiet. - I told you!
I seasoned it.
Seasoning
(He just keeps going for his forced jokes.)
You're good.
(Annoyed)
- Hold on. - Seasoning
He's not a professional.
(Annoyed as well)
- Actually, - I...
- he didn't do anything much. - He didn't do anything.
(A merciless critique by the cold eyes)
You think you can win against me, right?
(Plus an old man's provocation)
- You can't beat me. - I think he'll win.
(Cinderella Heo is fired up.)
Let's see when it's time for bed.
(Clenching his teeth)
Are you sure you'll be okay, Kyung Hwan?
(The moonlit night of revenge began.)
- Hold on. - You're really...
(Preparing a solid defense to survive)
Let's not fight each other.
Let's crush Jae Seok's.
(Betraying right away)
(No one should be trusted.)
Where are you going?
He woke up.
(The only thing you can trust is your gut.)
Let's sleep in peace.
(A loyalty-breaking showdown among eight men and women,)
Where... No way!
(with sleep completely out of the question)
(Facing the ultimate hidden mission for the reckless players,)
- What is this? - I thought it was weird.
- Don't get worked up. - Kyung Hwan.
(the last thread of reason snaps.)
Please!
- Give it to me! - This isn't right.
(After a wild night of madness, will the morning bring victory?)
- How are we going to sleep? - I have nothing.
I can stay up all night.
(Rip and Crush Cheorwon 2)
(Running Man)